From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight.
Truth's get told, it goes unfold, we stir the soul with a T-Serve code.
Trolls de-droppin', spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like we awake and step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so big play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like we awake and don't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream live from the madness, this ain't no dream
It's 9pm lights up, Mike's hot chaos in the stream
Vita calling in, slurring words, starting up the scene
Talking all that trash, then she flips Rage Queen mad at me
Girl, please, the show runs on caffeine
Scythe's twisted laughing, loud whiskey in his veins
Slur's flying left and right, we cut the feed, no shame
But the chat's on fire, can't tame this flame
This ain't your mama's podcast, this a runaway train
Alex tried to joke, boom, sent into the night
Panel looking sideways, someone's gotta fight
Producers on mute, praying this don't spike
Diamonds feeling spicy, shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink, that's no ho-
Kitty cat.
Yo.
Whoa, I love the green glow right there.
It looks like green glow.
All right, I'm gonna try to like put this over here.
Let me see, let me see.
I'm gonna hang out with my little alien friend.
He understands me.
Oh, God.
But it's a little bit bright,
a little bit bright for you, it's too bright.
It's a bright guy.
Hey, Mr. Brightside.
It's my wife, yes, it's very nice.
Sorry, it's Barack.
Hi Chanel, hi guys.
Freepiest fuck, I love it.
Oh, hey brats, you a kitten.
Hello.
That's what I imagine it sounds like.
So yeah, I'm just a little bit disappointed
in what I'm seeing right now.
I'm seeing, first of all, this idiot.
Retard Tom flash whoever this person is
He was just a beat as I thought I was just lurking in the chat and he said oh
Someone said oh psyche psyche has beef with everyone, which is not true
I don't have beef with anybody except for everyone if I can go away off on me and then
Tom's like oh, he's like I know he does that's why I try to take him as I took him down
Okay, well first of all you asshole you didn't take me down
You didn't take anything down if I need to take down that stupid look on your face. You you
Go away, you're talentless, not funny, nobody likes you on the show and you're a band.
Stay away you motherfucker, don't ever post anything like that on my show again, you
stick fuck.
Hi babe.
Yeah, he put like some very inappropriate, like you know, he's like very illegal, like
you know, he's the worst kind of porn, right?
What's wrong?
You want some attention too?
The alien bringing another cat, the alien's bringing you another cat.
Oh gosh guys, oh my god, you know and be like I love you be that you're you're there making fun of me, too
You know I thought I know. Oh
Jim's it doesn't eat hearts because she could just yeah, I don't eat hearts either
I don't know if you do anything to do with some criticism. You know really I
Mean geez. Yeah, bro. I would has their little inside jokes, right? They're not funny
Well, maybe they, maybe they are, it's, they're not.
It's like, I mean, it's like from the outside looking in,
it looks retarded to me.
I don't know.
It's like a bunch of,
oh really?
Well, Mermaid, you don't believe everything you hear, okay?
How am I scamming?
Explain it to me.
I wanna hear exactly so I can defend myself.
No allegations, no.
No, yeah, there you go.
Thank you, Jamie. Jamie knows exactly what I want.
He said, I didn't refund some cash. Wrong. Who? Fine. Tell me, tell me who. Every single person that has ever asked for a refund,
I've refunded every single person.
So tell me that their name. Dr. Tom Flash. He has five people acting like him. No, I just saw him in the I just saw him in
Dita's chat. It was a real Tom Flash and
He said he took me down. He's trying to take me down. So he goes to get any know I was there. So
It's okay mermaid mermaid, there's there's just lying it's a little lying
Are you he said he was like but he said he's like I'm live right now when he was in the chat
But I don't know people I guess anyone can say that I don't know
But he's he can be live and he can still be on his computer like saying stuff like I don't know if I looked him the other night
He was just sitting there on his computer
Whatever
Okay, well, okay. Well, I just I just don't like it
I mean it was somebody like he said his name was Tom flash in the other room talking to people like and they're all like
They know him and he's saying
Okay, well, I don't know. Was it his voice whose voice was that is that Canada dry? Do you think?
Yes, I do believe God is good. I believe in divine justice. I believe everything will be made right if not in this life
To the next one for sure
Someone is using OBX. I saw him on his channel. I want to live in totally different background. I don't know
OBX I don't even know what that means
I know but it's like guys it gets me all
Irritated well, I'm not even that irritated. I don't know
But guys you see why do you see why I like to charge for the panels panels are just totally like
The thing is, I don't even know.
Nothing, no conversation I was involved in, certainly.
You can see how I'm kind of pushed out of the conversation.
And, right?
That's fucking a little bit, yeah, man.
So are we okay guys?
I mean, it's like, it just seems like,
it's like, why is it so, why did the panel
got to be so smart me, is that a word smart me?
And it was like, not, well, it's fine, I guess.
It was sponsored, so.
But I do have to object to the program. Yeah, I think I prove it. But yeah, you know page left
I mean pages is this sponsor. I don't think I'll open it again. I'll give her that last two hours
That hit the end to the form bomb and stuff. I'll give it to her whenever she asks for it. So
Okay
And then she can run the panel because it's like it seems like everyone's like get her
It seems like people like are trying to like impress her by like picking on me or something. I don't know
Just put it this page like me or does it hate me? I don't know
That's just how we were friends
but
Are you welcome to the madness enjoy the ride
Yeah, that's true
Well, then we buy that guy that guy's big feels or whatever the guy's name the guy that was like had the finish
I wonder I mean, that's why it's also better to do one on the with a one-on-one
But even she she didn't like the one I think she I think she doesn't want even talk to me
She wants to talk to you when they open the battle
People are so weird
It's like I'm said I pour love into people I pour like I pour it I cry from her for my heart
Like my cuffs keep getting it kicked over
Sebastian yeah
Okay, I did six fields six freedom Roy
But okay, just awesome
Be hateful one day and see how it goes
God, I mean, it's like I have I have felt no I have
You know, I have been in that angry
State before like when I was probably a teenager and that you know the teenage years and felt very rejected by society, but
And I and I thought I was a Satanist basically
Don't think I can yeah, I kind of faked it. Oh
But yeah, that's when I was really like, yeah, I was like really like, you know down on humanity
I was like, oh, you know, man's just another animal and all kind of stuff and it's just like but it is like not a good way to
I just see where it leads in the world and that's it led to some bad bad things, you know
That's what I was like God. He I used to say I'm the only Christian Satanist like in the like actually like I was like
I'm so into Jesus
Love his message and then I think and then then I like had all the sympathy for the devil or also
I'm a Capricorn Capricorn is the devil, right?
Well, love is just as strong as emotion is hate you can really work a lot of magic with love rather than hate
I mean you can always alchemy stuff
Well, I think that's not a way to be and that's like you know Prowley did say that you know in the
Book of the law. He's like, you know, oh, you know
Just like here's the woman like the woman scarlet woman supposed to kill her own heart and this means it's just like that
that's who he's like is it is uh is
His ideal was this it's a heartless someone a heartless woman, you know, it's like and that's not the ideal of
the world I think heart is a very
Attractive thing, especially in this world where there's just so much hate anyway
So you got to join the Catholic Churches to hook up with some of the creed creed the women
Yeah, well you can do it just a hundred bucks, you know to let a questionnaire you can then contact the
Contacting the local grotto
Yeah, I know it'd be sacrifice to bella
I think the only real sacrifice are the ones we make ourselves not the not the one
people that think they can take somebody else's life and sacrifice somebody else's
life and that's gonna they're gonna get some kind of spiritual something or
some I don't know I don't know right well there's I mean that's I mean it's
basically all lesser beings it's like but you know it's I mean there's like
God's with a G right lowercase g I
Don't like to look at people. I mean we are we do contain all the animal
We're much more than an animal. We are like all the animals. We're all the animal including even more than the animal
Like we animals can't
Consider these things. They can't they can't they don't think oh is there but why am I here?
What's the purpose that all they can do is just be right it can just be like the
Shedded to the Aztecs. Okay, so Arbiter the Aztecs are not real
They were just another invention. I'm sorry to tell you that most of the stuff was built
It's probably about 200 years ago in the 1800s and they're faking the Mayan and Aztec stuff
Sorry to it. Sorry to burst your bubble guys
Not real
This universe, there's God and there's Iron Maiden, the Alpha and Omega, okay.
Okay, Iron Maiden, Alpha and Omega, okay. So that sounds like Alpha and Omega, that's a duality,
right? The God is a singularity, there's also the Trinity, right? If you don't figure out why you
are here by now, there is a problem. Why? I think, are we supposed to remember it? Do you think, does
my brain have my past memories in it where I can figure that out? All I can do is go by intuition
They'd like to fuck and fuck with us, you know, I'm talking about they like, you know, some God
They like to put us in like they are like a worst enemy or our mom and stuff like that and are like, you know
our best friend
Or you know on a library and stuff like so
They'd like to like it like to switch rules around and stuff like that
Mary is the Mariah are you talking about the Mariah Mariah
It's like the it's like the internet the deep dark web Mariana trench. We're talking about. Oh, Mary. Yeah, Mariana
or Mary Ann
Mary Ann Mary Ann, I would make a cute name for Elsa her name is you Mary Ann. I love that name
There's a hole in my heart as deep as the well of the poor boy
We suck halfway to him. Yes, Mariana's trench. Yep
Yeah
He knows
Mariana's trench. It's very dark. They're very dark sticky. Oh my god. I hate smart. I know it smug smarmy
I don't like this the superior like this. Oh, I'm better than I never stand better than
I'm the universe is from Iron Maiden Slayer the alphabet Omega's. I don't know. I don't get it
What was over the 200 years ago? Oh, yeah, but that's the Arbiter. That's history. I called history
It's not like real
But I'm saying maybe okay, so maybe there were mines and Aztecs, but I'm saying those the temples like the temple of the moon
Those were just recently built. It's like Disneyland. I can prove it to you, too
Go you can go to a channel called Vicky
Vicky s I have to check it real quick. Okay, there's a channel on YouTube called Vicky and there's a video called
I'll go find it real quick
Does it work yet?
You guys hear me?
Better?
Do you hear me?
Anyway, anyway, I was just at Vita's
and she was like, it seems like I was being talked about
because I saw, okay, I heard, you know,
my name was being brought up in the chat,
like I was reading it.
You can't rewind in her chat
but I could see my name was being mentioned.
And they're like, oh, it's always like the worst people that you they that or the people that present themselves the best that
Approve that that are the worst people they're like they're like page page psyche and beta or something like that
It's very rude, right? And it's like, okay, so I don't know what that what that was said and then
you know, they're just
I say I say it was there and I say it is like, you know
He was a nice guy my nose
What is that?
This is my hair. This is my hair. It's not my it's not. It looks like fun, right? This is my hair. Oh
My god, it looks like a stream coming to my nose. Okay. What? Okay, when I got my nose upticks
I could pull out plastic surgery stitches from it
It's pretty pretty gross. Yeah, so anyway
Yeah, so anyway
if you are interested in seeing like a little bit about history about how some things are a little bit
psychological operations or like that just go watch this video you'll see like you'll see the
Phoenician influence on the Mayans like where they have like little fish and the shells the Phoenicians
love the shells right okay yeah thank you it's just it's okay this wasn't a it wasn't a boogie okay
okay uh okay
Guys, okay, so but I just want to make sure page. It's okay if we do you want to do page pages to our
Are you here page you can do the let your rest of yours or I can start a I can start arbiters panel
Are you ready arbiter?
Guess I'll start arbiters unless you tell me differently. You can have you can have yours next time you tell me
Okay, you just fix your banner arbiter and I'll put the I'll put the panel up
Thank you, Arbiter, for your supporting the panel.
Arbiter did donate some very generously last night,
and so I do want to award him on the panel.
So if you'd like the banner to say anything goes,
besides just your name, OK?
Let me know, OK?
I'll keep it open until 2 a.m. Okay, for sure the guaranteed okay
It was if you want me to put in a particular color or if you'd like me to
Put a specific thing like a link or something or like I know your name or message anything you want in it
Okay, so it's like 2 a.m. PSC. Okay, just let me know and I will I got you bro. Okay?
And thank you again for your donations.
OK, I appreciate you very much.
OK.
Panel is now open.
Here is the link.
I will pin this right away.
Oh, shit.
we're all good. The page comes, oh come on. There you go, there you go arbiters.
Let me put the link up and we're, we'll get the show on the road.
Guys, can you just do me a favor, just be respectful and like, you know,
please um, I don't know, some of these, I don't know, just the general attitude.
Seems like it's like a nasty self-cafe page is doing her show right now. So we are starting arbiters panel
And then page will be next time. Okay
Go make sure you go say hi page two pages. Um
Great just great lives. Okay
Give me some pin the link and I'll let you write in. Okay
Hey, psych goes how are you?
I did not I should have probably watched a little bit more before I said that but I don't I don't want to ensure
Don't pay this thing at all. Oh, no, no, you're not you're fine. No, you're not you never intrude on me like you're fine
I'm just a little I'm just a little crabby right now
Just because of like there's like some kind of rude stuff that I've got me and people run in the mouth about you
I heard or something. Yeah, and no no in there like there's like not one person is defending me
Like not one person says anything there and they're not even beta and you think that beta that it's like she's it's like doing it
too, I mean it's so so
No, it's not right. That's why you don't trust that's why you don't trust people. That's why I
I wouldn't send it you easily even if I don't even even if we argue you offset there and defend you have done it many of times
Yeah, I mean
By the way, but I'll point that out, but thank you. I like you too and
You know, I uh, you know by the way that hair that hair you're gonna have to come it back because it did look bad
I look like you had a boogie
Oh, yeah
Where are they talking shit about unless you don't talk about it, what do they say?
Yeah, that better
Yeah, yeah, you're good brother. Good. Thank you. Yeah, let's get the show on the road
Yeah, well, I love the traveling it doesn't have a traveling show
I think about this show is I can travel and do the show if I was successful enough
I could like go on the road and with my laptop and then
Long you should not think about Starlink. I'm pretty sure you can get that shit anywhere
Mm-hmm. The Starlink. Yeah, I was there's these guys on on YouTube
They're like you did you prank calls and stuff like that, but they like live in the middle of like the woods and
I'm not the message users, but they live it
But it's like it's like they have like little tiny home there
And then it's like they have like this Wi-Fi setup
So they have like the Wi-Fi and then they go down to like, you know get food once in a while
But I see my homestead guy do it and he lives in the middle of nowhere and he had a Starlink
And I tell you what it came in better than my fucking Wi-Fi does
So the bass they have bass is darling. I mean, I'm never like this was this was this was like a couple years
Like he had like a we he set out a thing now
I don't think you have to do that because there's so many satellites up there now
I don't think you have to like set anything up. It's direct to your phone
He put on that tree that he could yeah
Yeah, that's the best place are tall but hey Sebastian we ended the stream because I got I got bombed by somebody that says they were the Tom Flash guy
I don't think it's one of the people said it's not him
But uh, there was somebody named Tom flash in Vita's chat saying oh, I just took down psyche or turn trying to take down psyche or something
So anyway, that's what he's an automatic fan. I would hope yeah
But I've been isn't people are like, oh, that's a fake one and so I don't know
It's like who knows I mean it's so hard to
You want to talk about psyche way if you don't talk about this
We want but they were running their mouth about you tonight or what's going on?
Well, I just think I mean you said something about like a bad guy like
Well pages one but that guy like paid psyche and stuff. I heard you say something about it
So what somebody said that somebody's that was a comment in one of the chats like they're like, oh, you know, like, you know
I think I thought he said I think it was like
Not maybe zimp ulcer. I'm not it was somebody from my
What was their argument? How are you a bad guy? I don't
People that seem the nicest are like are like really like bad or something
It was just like that was that's this one comment. I read but then there was other comments like the Tom flash guy
And then the general thing that I say on the panel, I say is probably mad at me because I like, you know.
Didn't want to
He like just kind of bums me and so then I just like kick him off the stream sometimes then you'll just add back page
I don't I don't get the argument with them though
I just in the spot I asked them like how is he about you like how is he a bad guy?
I don't know
They're like they're like they're like talking like really
Upset about it. Yeah, it's because you're a YouTube creator. They're gonna talk shit. They have no arguments. They're not gonna
Like the dude's name is flash. That's what he does. I mean, that's way more harm than what you do
You don't do no harm. You run a fucking YouTube channel. No, I don't show whatever you show and you know I'm saying
Yeah, it was like easily it was it it was really it wasn't even it was beyond porn
It was like a beyond inappropriate. It was like, you know, it was they kind of like the
Corinlon lens of the Epstein stuff, you know, oh, you gotta do let me put you a little some game real quick
They say like oh sights bad, but they say like
Ghosts bad person just ask them how that's your first question like how am I that person and then if their answer is dumb
Then you can burn them up, but if your answer is kind of a little bit smart
You got it you then you can hit him with like what do you mean by harm and then you can get into it
You know you can debate them. I mean, it's not that hard
Yeah, I know when all debate bros or nothing, but I mean like it call me a bad person. Well, how that's the first thing you got to answer
Well, you have to ask the first thing they have to answer and then when they do answer you can see where they are
They just dumb or they ask you debating then you can get into it
You know I'm saying yeah, no reason to be upset about it. They had no I'm not
It's a plane. They don't know what the fuck they're talking about
You know people are gonna talk shit
Yeah
I know but it's like but why have game up on me? It's like I mean it's like and then it's people narrative
They act like it's like you want to go back over there. I'll go over there with you
I'll have you back. You want to go back over there?
We can like we maybe like just like see what's going on there, but I don't want to like
I don't I don't I probably want to introduce obviously I just I just want to lurk in here
I wish they would be listening they come over here because
But someone's gonna go run over there and say thank you said he's gonna come sit in your chat and like she's
No, I didn't say that go said that like he never once said that let's get it correct
Yeah, but I'm gonna say something like that like oh
Coming over here, but uh, you know, I don't know until the next time beta's crying wasn't to be on the I wouldn't let her back
I don't know if it's like we're cool and then it's like she just like seems like she just like looks down on me
She's like seems like she's in that mouth a little too much though
Because look I had that I had why would she not have your here's my question
I don't mean interrupt, but why would she not have your back? I don't know I don't get it
I guess she's over me, but I made that for I made that like in her honor. I got a tattoo. I got like fucking
You know, it's been nothing wrong
Especially not to her, but I don't know maybe she's done with me. Hey, Kirsten. How are you?
Because it's like she's like I seen
I see no in the chat. Yeah, it's like sir
It was just like it seemed like she was kind of like
It's like this is looking down on me or something like that. I don't like that feeling
I'm very I'm very pick up on this thing
Were you part of the were you in the background or were you part of the I was just I was just working in this
I didn't say anything in the chat. No, I just
Talking shit. You're not even part of it. You're just working. They're talking shit
Bad it's like they don't they don't think I'm like watching or something like that
But yeah, if you've already told me that they're talking
You know what if I was you brought wouldn't even have said nothing tonight either let that shit go
Next time she tries to join your fucking panel. It had been ex communicator
I had a fucking blocker and then I would have talked my shit while she's watching you
Yeah, she was
She cried and want it back on the panel members
She's done it fucking so many times cry about it and what back on the panel and you'd let her up and
People were like don't let her back up. Don't let her back up
But you did out of the goodness of your heart you did and so she's crazy
Well, yeah, I guess it's you a lot of best friend best friends and love and women
They're next got daggers down. That's why I keep so no loyalties. You've learned the hard way
Yeah, I really did because it's like
I mean, it's like I have to do have to go solo. It's gonna be because it's basically like everyone's saying, you know
And that's like I need people to say, you know, they're like, you know, they're on team psyche or whatever, right?
You're okay. Yeah, but because I don't know it's like, you know
People said team psyche and then they just they turn around and they do it. There's all this
Way, I'm in opposition. We argue many of times how many times we argued. I mean many many at times
But I don't go on other people's channel and talk shit about you
Right even if we're literally fighting I'll literally defend you
It's not there. I do like you. I do like to argue though. Sorry
No, it's okay. I was wondering if Daryl is a bad dick Daryl. Were you over there?
Did you see anything interesting going in the chat or just did you pick up on like that?
I was being talked about he was like, I'm not a psychic or anything
But you know, it's like it's kind of like in a sarcastic way and then they're like, oh, well
I'm gonna charge you a dollar a minute like I'm charging people a dollar a minute for the show or something like no
I'm not I mean I donate it and never once got charged
the
Yeah, I mean people have for I mean people have for hours and hours. I've never like
Like put one cent towards the show. It hasn't been over a year yet. It's probably been over a year. I think I don't know
I've been doing just the open panels. You seem to be this chat sheep. Yeah, I've been doing open panels since January
I've been doing the streaming since probably October or September October and last year I started streaming like just once in a while
I wish you would run the beta channel and then say
If anybody wants to do it, they can come bring $10 jump on the panel and we'll handle it easy
Easy work. I know I know anybody on that panel easy work easy
Well, the panel is not you know, it's like the person use you so you sponsored the panel for everybody
So the panel is open people could come up now, but it's a key, but it's it's either banner
I have yeah, so you got the banner and so that's how that's how like the so it works guys
It's just like, you know, it's like a there's
There's like any block that will charge like
You know, if you have TTS, you know, it will be like, you know, pay a few bucks and they have whatever you want to say on the screen
Well, if you want to like have like whatever you want to say on the screen on a banner for like three hours
Here's the way to do it. You know, it's like it's not too much more
I sponsor it to have it open just don't let no porn bombers come up here
But anybody else that wants to join please feel free. I mean psych am I okay with saying that?
Yes, yes
Because I want the open debate I'm there talk man. I get I get you Sebastian I get you I know I get I get your point
There's Sebastian, but you know here. I really get a guess. Well, hey say
It's stay turn you don't got to put up the little wall. You're good. You're good. Okay?
So it says he says I give my time in I provide the entertainment for free I do for my own and I hope
Help to have a good show. Yes. And the people that do that, but there's people that are like bad panelists. You understand? And they're on for hours
KZ for example, he was just a terrible panelist like never had really anything interesting to say just mumbled and
And you know and then he just wanted to be
That's another guy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
And then now I don't let it on the panel like one time because I'm
Instituting this program and then he's like oh, I'll put the banner up and then he's like oh my god
He's like you're fucking the phone you fake you're going off on me about that
Like what's the hell? It's like wow. Wow. I should and I was always defending him like over all that stuff
You know, she would always say no
Okay. Yeah, here we go. I'll put you here
Hi guys, what's up, Turk?
What's going on? What's going on? It's like how you're doing? Oh
Night, brother. How we doing?
I'm talking to psyche goes full back for a minute. Wait just wait
Well, I didn't I didn't raise my fucking hand to have a churn and I'm talking
What do you mean? You don't need to raise your psyche was addressing me state turn you are we both were you're
No, we both were addressing you
Did I not just say hey?
I
Don't come on for no reason. You're like a woman, but I do not want to argue with you. Let's start fresh. How about that?
Just to show I'm not aggressive. I'm not here to fight
For none of that. How about that? We'll start over. Um, psyche my day was great. How was your day, bro?
Very good. I made a couple of the AI videos for my you know my show and I'm really excited with them
You know, I'm having a good coffee a couple coffee
I love them bro. The Alex one
That's what cracks me up. Um, and you win the arm Joe shipply that shit cracks
Them sisters crazy. I love them bro. It's funny. It's gay, but I like it's funny. I mean, I don't like
comedic
Well, yeah, yeah, the trip kick ones like trip or like the Joe Shipley one trip kick made for me and then I
Produce the yeah, the the Alex one. Yeah, it's like really cool
Like and also the right yet guys everyone has to try chat GPT
It's free and it's like just go talk to talk to it. It'll give you so many good ideas
It's like helping me with so many things right now. I'm like, oh my god
It's like having an assistant almost like
pretty crazy. I'm glad we started over again. Do I have permission to go on the panel that I paid for?
Yeah, that's sorry. Well, stay turned. Is it okay for that to have permission on
talking to the panel that I paid for? Is it okay? My silence is your cue.
Well, you know, your silence is pretty, maybe you should practice it a little bit more, brother.
Oh, come on, come on, guys.
You guys are so silly.
Yeah, well, that's one of the things
that witchcraft is like.
To dare, to will.
Is there like something a spell would
wake in the sleep?
I mean, I'll cook it up.
Yeah.
It goes, it's called a zippa-lulipa.
I'm just kidding.
Oh, zippa-lulipa.
Oh, I like it.
Okay, so the intro was made with another website.
Okay, so ChatGPT, I put in like what I wanted for the song.
And ChatGPT put the lyrics, and then I put the song lyrics through like another A, I think,
that makes it into music.
And then I take the music, and then I put that into another A, I think,
and that turns into a, yeah, it's up.
It was 10.30 last night, as I believe, right?
Yeah.
And so, yeah, so then it comes out with a video
and it's like, it's really,
I put like just a little bit of input into it,
but for the little bit I do put in there,
it really takes it and runs with it.
And so pretty cool.
And the one I use for the video is called Neural Frames.
If you guys wanna check out that video,
but I warn you is a little bit pricey
because it uses credits,
like instead of just a monthly fee.
Upgraded so I got more credits, but it's expensive. Okay a site guy
I just wanted to come up here and tell you real quick before like on I had sister
I said something in the comments earlier. I was like, uh
I said I said something to the effect of like oh shit beaters doing numbers right now, whatever the case was
And and then you you said something like oh everybody go support beta and it ended the panel like
Wasn't trying to like recruit people or go. I know I was just talking, you know
Can I talk to psych for a minute
Yeah
You know you do all this talking, but you never say anything you do a lot of talking, but you don't say
Can I get a minute? I can't how much money you got go ahead
20 I'll be quiet brother
I'll put them here the left side.
They mentioned her.
If you can hear me.
That wasn't a jab.
It wasn't everybody.
Fuck psyche, go to beaters.
All I said was a beaters doing numbers.
She had like 70, 75 in the chat.
I'm like wow.
That's all I said.
Didn't I did
Shit about him over there. So I honestly wanted to I want to say wanted to like say hey
Let's like go over there like it's like it was like I'll go over there be on her panel and like
Yeah, yeah, I was actually over there conversating with you. I didn't see you in the comments, but I was
Because no, because you you like you said you was like gonna hop over there and what's all you was like everybody go over there
You said I'm a hop over there. I actually was talking to you in the comments, but you know, I didn't get
No, I did not know I did not dickhead
What would you say you my claim wasn't that my claim wasn't that you talked shit. What's it?
I said they close your you're just fucking exhausting man. Fuck you fucking claims and fucking the
And you can't debate for shit you suck at it. Why are you over here?
I'm you're over here because it's open panel and I respect it, but
I'm over here for the same reason you're here. Okay, how do you talk shit about us like how do you feel about that?
How do I feel about what there until now?
You heard what I said. No, I didn't hear what you said. I heard how do I how do you feel about?
Something talking shit about like who I didn't hear who
It wasn't like it wasn't it wasn't our chat kind of and like and she was and she was like saying she said like little things like
Oh, she's like, well, you know, oh, she doesn't need cards to read it to be psychic
She's very intuitive and very talented artist and then she said oh and and she's like
Oh, and you know, I'm gonna charge you a dollar a minute to be on panel now to the people like kind of like just like it
But those are both I think chabs at me, but I wasn't even talking in her cat. Yeah, it's a lot better be the same. Yeah. Yeah
Don't they did
My name is mention my name is mentioned in the chat like people were saying stuff about and then they also said
I mentioned you in the chat I was taught but I thought I was talking to you
I said what I right now what I'm saying to you right now about yo site
Why did you end the live type of shit? That's what I said to you in the chat
I'm like damn site. Why'd you end the live all I did was say be the head. You know me and she was doing
But I
Like I don't even know her like that first of all I only know her through you so
If anything, I know you more than I know her like you give them saying yeah
It was just like the last thing was like that's like Andrew was in his life right now. We should all go there and watch
He's doing numbers
You go to Andrew you go to Andrew
that's where you go go to go to where on sites being not going anywhere see
that's going to read though to mention other people's like other YouTube people on a channel like
If you're worried about Vegas so much just go over there
Yeah, well, it's like, you know, anyway, I'm okay. I'm okay. I was in the kind of a weird move because I was really trying to like say
Hey, let's like go support her like right now. Like, you know, I guess she was on I didn't know she like I
Watch her in like a few days and I went over there like ready to like, you know
We're going the panel or joint and it's like a gym. They can there's I say there who I just kicked off my show and
You know, they're just making things like little. I don't know. I pick up on stuff, you know, maybe I'm too sensitive
But, uh, yeah, it was just it was just right before I came on the live. I just went straight from there to here
Yeah
Thank you. Yeah, because someone said, um, oh you they're like, oh
They're like a psyche I had a beef with everyone someone said and then Tom flashed in the chat said oh, I know
That's why I I took him down tonight or something like that. It's like she like he was like some kind of yeah
That's a good argument. He's too sensitive. Sure. I showed my I can't say the word and I broke TLS and I took him down
It's your mark sunset of the he is you know the fuck you're talking about so you have to show something
He doesn't know I love these people to come over here. I love a little piece of them
Yeah, well, I don't think they probably won't go to the piece of who a piece of what like what are you talking about goes?
Pretty sure I just said it
But like every time you get into any type of
Somebody they fuck you up
Okay, who fucked me up name one person
Me me me
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
who is us, who is us, you're saying us like you're part of a gang, who is us, who's us
well I did sponsor the panel so
I'm an individual
right now I'm part of us
and you're retarded
right, who is us
right now you're part of who's us, who, you and who else, you and who else
This is my panel dum-dum psyche
Correct, this is your
All right, okay, that's cool. That's cool. You sponsored it. All right. Yeah, you just lost dumb dumb
Why don't you go
You ain't gonna win
Hold on a psyche. Is this your channel or is this my it's my it's my channel
Yeah
Yeah, I when people sponsor it, I like to give them a chance to like, you know, um
To have some kind of feeling of ownership for the panel too so they can help like, you know
You're people that are trying to like, you know porn bomb or like
That's what you need to do you need to stay the fuck
What does that mean stay shut
Shut your mouth shut your mouth. Yeah, you mean stay shut the fuck up. You're doing how to finish the symptoms
No, just stay shut stay shut just quiet like what do you know?
When you was in when you was in grammar school, were you in the trailers did they put you in the trailers?
Did you have to wear a helmet?
Did you have to wear a mouth guard like that's the kind of vibes you're giving me
Cool and check the score how many times where I won against you we can check
Ghost is a part of you, you're literally like, you're literally a second alice, that's how we part of you, you're third to zero, check the scores, smoking on a state trip back here, and I'm tired of smoking on it, ah, ah, ah, ah, tired of smoking on it, you're, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, y'all need, I need a better, yeah, I'm tired of smoking on it, but you're not even supposed to be up here, why, you're not even a contender, sir, so guess what, pay to get me banned.
Hey, give you already paid $25 ban me for 24 hours. How about that money begging again?
$25 ban me out of here. Get me the fuck out of here for a whole
More than $25 after no panel. Do you have your ass up here? You're welcome by the way
Fuck you fuck you when you welcome this. I don't give a fuck about your welcome this bitch
Well, then if you feel unwelcome then just leave I could but you could pay $25 to make it happen. You are
Don't need don't need matter of fact don't even put it through the arm the the super chat
Let him get the whole 25 and get me up out of here pussy. Do it
Matter of fact, that's a good question. How much would it be to kick me out since I fucking sponsored this?
During your time, I won't kick you up during the time I won't kick you up
You know what donate a hundred dollars nature and I'll leave go ahead
I don't want you to leave. You're my favorite
Shut the fuck up boy. You ain't shooting on nothing. You're
Another I want another pack. I'm also my betas people one another pack. What you want here
Yeah, all right
What's your argument dumb dumb go ahead and make it
You're not gonna do it already
I'm not a debater
If you got a topic I will fuck you up in a debate and I never debated in my life. I promise you I'll fuck you up
Well, you talk a lot of shit run your mouth
Are you sure you never debate it are you sure?
No, I get busy like I get busy for real like so I do talk shit
Check the scores. I'll put you on the shirt. Oh boy
Put me on this and put me on an e-shirt
That says like R.I.P. Stay turn or do whatever the fuck
You know me like do what you got to do
Think about I never thought about you
I don't I don't know I don't know who the fuck you are not gonna care about my body
You got hose nope, I didn't think you do yeah
So what's your argument?
Oh, I'm done with this clown. Oh my god.
Okay, then my god, you can leave.
I'll switch it up a little. You can leave.
Why don't you go back and talk shit about Psyche, by the way,
because you've done it. You've done it.
I know you've done it. How about this? How about this?
How about this? If you could pull up any message or clip
that I talk shit about Psyche,
I'll bounce myself for free. How about that?
Well, no, because I don't watch their shit like that. I don't replay it. No, but you know the claim any you got to make the claim
You made the claim you got to put the
Bro
Pull up the evidence family
Proof pull up your burden of proof do that do that please do it please
You'll never find on
Yeah, how are you your friend? Who's your friend all being friend? Hello? You're muted, sir
Sir you muted. That's a man
What you did say you scared away
Yeah
Can you hear me? Yes
No, I'm not sure you guys up to
Hanging out. Yeah
What is it Monday night? I'm his coffee and stuff. You want to smoke some weed?
Yes
You want to you want a beer? Yeah, how can I be more accommodating?
My dog seems to like you
Do you have a tail? I was talking to the dog
Let's talk to the dog. Oh
Oh shit
This is my friend psych psych this is my friend. Oh, it's alien light. Hi
You know who you are right now, where are you? Hello nice to meet you LD and friend
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it's a little you're obviously don't hang out. What do you want? That's better. It's better. It's better better. Thank you
Is that better?
Yes, the mustache is better here
My mustache looks better
Devin the importance on my stuff. I'd love it. He likes the mustache
Yeah, she wants the mullet too she wants me extra white trash
Oh
Show them the dreads. Oh, look at the look at look at those lovely shirt. Look they're glow in the dark
Weird I found her on the side of the road. So I was like, hey, oh my god, how much you pay for I guarantee
Years ago, so I found her in the trash 20 years ago
I used to date her like 20 years ago, but that should have, that should have stayed 20 years ago, years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have left you there, I used to date her like 20 years ago, but that should have, that should have stayed 20 years ago, years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, should have been a mistake, I would have stayed 20 years ago, should have been
I
Listen, that's a listen. That's a pretty looking woman right there
Can I show me your back?
I love your back tats you okay show it to them
that's not the way you talk to the way you talk to evade them
I
Said was a lady I would actually be I'm back to a lady. It's not a lady. Yeah, she was a lady
How yeah, how is she a lady?
Just a jewel. Have you ever seen a jewel?
Kind of looks like it. I'm not gonna lie now. I kind of feel like a
it's like the fucked up the downsensum dot-coward a
Don't do it a great a great porn star in the 70s. He would have been a great porn star in the 70s, wouldn't he?
I mean gate for I wouldn't use that mustache now, but
I'm a lot more experienced now than
I have a lot less hair than you do.
Is he better at things?
Let me see, hold on.
He was doing experiments, okay?
Okay.
Does her hair not stink?
I'll just be honest with you.
That's my question.
Does her hair not stink?
Her hair does not stink.
My room is what stinks.
Smell it.
It probably stinks.
No, it doesn't stink.
I can smell it.
Look, you're asking smaller hair.
Fucking weirdo.
I did smell her hair.
You know, like you know, it's not expensive man. Like you're kidding. Oh, I mean like for that
I need a shot of my fireball and there ain't too much. You know, I do still drink fireball. Yes, I do
Why why doesn't that fireball on it? Let me see that bottle again. Yeah, let's see it again
Yeah, that's fireball
Yeah, it's fireball. It's the it's the drag. No, it's like their collector edition
Oh, I was about to say because I don't drink that shit, but I never see that label
Yeah, it's like they're a collectible. I don't know it's the same it's the same shit. It's just a different label
I want fireball the sponsor my stream
What are you doing girl
Sikey nothing towards you but ghost you're telling the woman to put some clothes on
I
What do you mean
A pretty woman oh put some more clothes on what
you know doing weird shit put fucking
if i was in the rexic would you would you so if i was in the rexic would you say i should
have no clothes on no i tell you go eat a sandwich i i'm exactly like i'm telling her
Oh, I don't fuck you pay me under my ass before I left the New Orleans session.
Oh, that's all she knows.
Oh, that's sad.
Oh, under your butt cheeks.
Yeah, I've seen that.
I don't think we can show that tattoo without getting a butt.
Yes, you can.
You totally can do it.
Without getting a porn show.
Don't do it.
Well, then go ahead show them. I mean if you want to I don't like it. Don't let them do it
Yeah, fuck you pay me
Okay, I like it. That's fine. You're good, psyche. That's you. Yeah, you're good. Oh, yeah
You don't know underwear. Yeah, is that ghost or any man's in the profile picture? Which profile picture? That's Luigi. Oh
No, I just spilled all my weed
Uh-oh, you're fine. You're fine. Oh man, bro
Here do you think the phone
You have two hours left two hours I'm ghost
Wow, thank God and you get the fuck out of here
You can leave any time you want brother feel free to leave
not even going to do to them to to all that was because you're not smart enough to have the conversation
Okay, stay trying you don't the fuck you're talking about you're too stupid to have the conversation
You already admitted that you're too stupid to have it. You don't know what the fuck a debate is
Bitch shut up. I'm talking to him if you don't mind real quick. Oh, yeah, we don't want to see here
We don't want to see your ass. We don't see your tattoos. What was she under water?
We don't see it speak for yourself
You don't like women doesn't mean the rest of us guys hit
Go ahead with your argument. I don't like to shoot this war out. I don't like women.
Bro, you actually argued my argument for me and won.
Go ahead with your argument, sir.
I'm down for an argument.
You put a point on my scoreboard.
Yeah, what's your score?
All right, I'll give you one last chance make your argument
I don't know you said are you here you said I'm too stupid to have the
So what why are you here?
You're a dumb dumb
Big on by state
Hey, go so I'm gonna tell you like this, right?
These people in the chest saying, oh, do you live with your mom?
I'm done with them.
I don't have a problem with people living with their moms.
Hold on.
That's all we're going to do.
I don't know what you're saying.
This is great.
It's been done with them.
I gave you a chance to get there.
My mom is telling you to stop yelling and stop screaming.
Keep on doing it.
You need to listen to your moms.
That's still your mom's room.
You're still living with them.
Your mom's room.
Okay
Thank you for emptying your bank account a little something
I don't want you
that's that's that's there where the other one no you got to pay for that
you only listen you only pay for it i'm dumb
oh you did was pay the spot to the parent
additional services require additional money
he called me first he didn't call me
and she didn't have to leave though, they didn't see her,
they just thought I don't know those bugs
for ground chief hunters at all.
Well, my words, psych's being wrong,
psych, are we not getting rid of him
because I'll deal with it.
Stay here.
You want me to go, Sank?
If you want me to go.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, not you, y'all be, you stay, by the way.
I'm talking to you.
You stay.
Sure.
Yeah
You're protected you're protected of it goes to but you know so it's like no one can no one can clap you well
It's your panel. Okay, so but I can't make it like I can't kick people off at your request though
So I have to like what was for dinner tonight's like what you have for dinner. Can you can you give my friend a tarot card reading?
She's from New Orleans. She believes all that
He's gonna give you he's gonna give you a tarot card reading
He's really good at it.
Oh, oh, oh, shit, big boy alive, bull.
Fuck him.
I'll give you one card.
It's called a roast beef.
It's not, it's not.
I'll do three cards, I'll do three cards for you,
and then like a word of advice card.
So that's such cool, right?
All right, all right.
You need to do a card rating.
Okay, here we go.
It's actually gonna be my first like you never you never okay, so my friends are terrible and stuff like that
And I've done terrible reading, but I've never had a reason. Oh, you never had a reading
So you're a virgin. Yeah
Okay, you know it. Let's let's do it. We're doing all sorts. Okay
Well, I'm seeing like a 10 of swords which means like a major betrayal
You had the major betrayal happens to you like stab to the back a lot of times
You maybe didn't even like know you're gonna make it through it or something like that
There's a see a major betrayal right there that happens
10 of swords if they get up
for you
Very harsh, but it looks like you've like gotten out of it and now it's like you know
Also, it's like you're doing like a better for yourself
And it's like and now you're able to like help people too and you're able to like
You know, give to the right people and help if you want to, okay?
Like this is generosity and also you have an increase in wealth, okay?
And then, okay, and then we have ten of pentacles.
And so ten of pentacles is like the opposite of the ten of sort.
Ten of pentacles is like that.
That generational wealth, it looks like it's going to continue to grow from the six pentacles to the ten of pentacles.
It looks like it's going to go in the right direction. This is like legacy.
This is like having everything you need comfortable, happy, okay?
The advice for you is the advice is the truth like tell the truth and like know the truth and like stand up for the truth
This is like ace of swords like the true part of truth
And so just always stand up for your truth and the truth in general and up. Yeah
So that's the advice for you. I do really quick readings, but I hope you like that
Thank you
Okay, oh
She knows about this this is called the it's called the Van Gogh deck and it has like the I think it's story night
Yeah, I show you all the cars you like this was the 10. I'm sorry. I thought I didn't show the cars. I'm sorry
There's a ten of stores
Which is like, you know someone's sat in the back and then there was
I might have shoveled it back in I'm sorry. Yeah, this six of pentacles
Yeah, it's a card of like just knowing where to knowing where to be generous like knowing who does who deserves it more and that kind of thing, right?
And then yeah, I showed you the truth card, but yeah
Yeah, I mean it's like but I definitely see like the wealth is increasing and it's like you're and it's like it looks like you recovered from whatever happened
It's like but it's like and I know like this tennis board is gonna be like people
I think that's the end the end but it's like it looks like you've like you've gone on and done or doing better, okay?
Thank you. Very nice. You're welcome. I'll have to send you some money for your reading side. I appreciate it.
Oh, no problem. My pleasure. Thank you for letting me read.
Once I've done with this one.
I got a little bit of what?
Why does the tennis swords have only seven swords on the on the card?
Oh, there was seven. Let me see
The other three are in my back
We'll see you said three you said the three of the three sources right there. It was very tough
It was right there
I think there's the 10 stores there, but see there's like, they're everywhere. See? Oh, no, no, I see that. No, it was a different one you showed. It was all like straight swords in a line.
Oh, that was, I think I said only said this one, it says, because it looks like like the 10 stores, but yeah, it was an accident.
Okay, that was, okay, what's going on in the chat?
Okay, hold on, let me fix this.
Oh, yeah, I see the wood like them. Yeah, it's a landscape mode, so I can show both of us because it's as hard as a whole for an extension.
You need to turn your camera, you need to turn your phone.
I did turn my phone.
Oh, I guess that's a little better.
Yeah, or you can do it like this because you want to take that.
Oh, and there are little boxes.
Yeah, that's a lot better.
Okay.
Yeah, we're going through the sky. They're like we're flying in the plane, right?
It's pretty trippy. Okay
Yeah, so I've been making some AI songs. I don't know if you heard any of the AI songs or the music in general
I've been doing. I'm sorry. I actually passed out there. I thought you were gonna give me a lot of black over there
I don't know where ghosts went guys. Ghost disappeared. Ghost disappeared
Okay, ghost ghosted us I think guys and so you know he's living up to his name
Yeah, he's crazy he's crazy
He did donate last night what you have for dinner tonight, uh, psych I had a glazed doughnuts. I have one left here
The cornerstone there's there's snacks there if you want potato chips or anything I mean, and I got like coffees too
I have lots of rocks and bagel and then everything I eat is like what the fuck is that?
That was a
Dona, it's really thick
Is it like cakey or is it like doughy?
He's in Cali.
It's doughy.
It tastes pretty doughy.
Garrett, it's because the seven of swords for this stick looks just like the regular ten
of swords, because it's usually in somebody's back, right?
It's horizontal.
Horizontal.
Right.
That's how that card was.
Like when they don't have the glazing it's the plain doughnut. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, like the absolutely no glazing looks a lot better.
It's super fried dough.
It's super...
Mmm, yummy.
Yeah, I don't like it.
It's dry. Do you like drink with it or something?
Don't get into my coffee.
That's how they came up with Dunkin Donuts, right? I mean, now you got donuts with everything on them.
That's not I had the best coffee. It was banana coffee. It was a banana coffee
I do like those Boston those Boston cream pies are pretty good. Oh, I love Boston. I love any kind of
cream-filled donut my favorite
Never hear the jelly donut
Is that a sexual thing? I think it's a sexual thing or something. It's when you come on a girl's face
So it's all white and you punch her in the nose. Oh my god
Discussing
Hey, yo, um
Hsieh
Tell me that ain't
So please tell me that ain't so I did see the picture. I did see the picture
Please say
I'm not going to say to show your feet to anybody.
So it's a batch of stop-action.
Stop-action.
Ah.
Yo shit.
That LD community.
Tell her to show her feet.
Terrible.
Guys, stop it.
Don't be so perverted, OK?
Okay, adorable female at LD not entitled no screaming and calm she doesn't seem really nice. He seems like super chill super chill
You would have been good on like a show like the real world, you know, like the real world
Okay, you put on mute. Okay. I don't know
Okay, well
We wouldn't trying to spy here. I'll just go on full screen. Oh
Let's see you want to see
Later, but like I have shirts that say like anal queen, but it looks really dainty and it's like
But then
Life and she like never says but letter points up to me like it's just very flea and when I was living in Vegas
We had this bodega on the corner and it was called murder mark or some guy got murdered in front of it
But when the neighbor called it murder mark and they used to sell t-shirts that said blowjob queen at the murder mark
Oh my god, I have, well, I have like, I had, I put on shoes, like, I made like really nice
font on shoes and it says font on the side, but then it says logo, please, like, you know, like,
covers, like, when you put your feet together in the front. So, yeah, I love that too. I love just, like, you know.
Like playing games over sexualized shirts that I shouldn't wear in public. Yeah. Yeah people people already over sexualized me
So I'm I've also laughed at it. Also, don't fucking banana. I love that shit since high school
I still have like a fucking tool hoodie and it was like two like bolts and then like a wrench
I look like a dick. You know, like you can't wear that in school. I'm like, are you kidding me?
And the other shit that I got sent home for was like
Stupid as shit
I remember my high school yearbook with a picture of me like Jim class sitting it out reading newspaper
I'm wearing a shirt says I only date milfs
He had blue hair and she's like put on the clown makeup and like I used to draw my eyebrows on
And he put his eyebrows with like two clown arches and he wore leopard print leggings
And just like, you know some kind of band be sure I was like you're they're giving you a lot of credit
Charisma says adorable female not entitled
LD LD so as far as I can see man, she's a keeper. She's a keeper
I guess I've used to date like 20 years ago, no, I'm 36, so it was like 15 years ago, but she's 29 years old.
I was like doing the math in my head and I'm like wait this ain't math at all.
I'm dying.
Definitely.
Yeah
Like I look older
I feel like I look like this guy is fucking picture
or my friend who I was like, you look so beautiful to me, but she didn't hear me.
That's very you.
She looked at the camera and I was like, okay cool.
that's such a brutal game to play at work I would have like everyone's
information and be like oh I know your date of birth like obviously it's right
here on your chart like I'd be like oh how old do you think I am my length
I put on a little bit of lipstick then, since we've dated, I put on like maybe five pounds.
That's barely, barely though.
It's my laugh lines.
I got really deep laugh lines from what it's my one.
You look like older for your age when you were younger when we were dating I was blonde when we were dating
I was also blond
I was blonde for a long time
Well, let me be respectful
How you doing? I'll be
You gotta ask permission to crash out you come on you sound stupid and then you say let me be respectful. What's up, LD?
I
Answer the question okay, do you have sure yeah, what's the question?
Long here
Okay, so is that you and um in in in one of the profile pictures in the chat? That's you. That's really you
Do it long hair short hair dumb dumb
It looks like so it looked like psyche's hair, but
OK, this is a hard question, not everything is a hard question, but you tell between you and me, you shut the fuck up when you talk to a person like me, y'all.
I never took my tail, I never took my tail.
Well, you're gonna talk it tonight.
You're gonna talk it, brother.
Shut the fuck up, what's your argument?
If you don't have one, stop talking to me, boy.
Go suck a dick, y'all.
I'm gonna talk to you.
Yeah, that's a good argument.
Let me talk to my dude out of the...
If you don't mind.
Keep talking about arguments and debates and nobody's trying to bait. Yeah
You're too stupid to have one sir, this is not a debate channel you dickhead. It's not a debate channel
which is channel that I sponsor and I
There is argument fucking
You should say open panel
Listen don't be overly loud and disrupt your mom's sleep bro. She's probably sleeping
Um
What's my mother's name ghost, where's my mother from ghost tell me tell me
Where's she from tell me
Cosme Daddy, you heard?
And where would my mother be from? Psyche, it's not Daxing. Don't worry about it. I'm initiating it. It's fine
Where's my mom from ghost since you know everything? Where's she from?
Just
Just not your panel
Why are you still here? I'm
I did
You want to think you rushed it get the fuck out of here
So your argument is like
Don't even talk don't even talk
My argument is no
Talk to LD I don't want you
LD's all yours go ahead speak
Listen sir, if you're stupid
Well, you chose the right hand
And not mustache
Before she came over
She's Muslim
No, no, she's Jewish oh
Fuck decide get them out. Get them out
Get them out. We're gonna break to us tonight
Precise uh, she's Jewish bro. No, we're gonna break to you. Yeah, bro. I went over her house for one
Yeah, what was the most recent one? Oh, yeah
That's why you look like a weasel I hear
She makes the best to filter fish. Hey, ma'am. How do you ma'am? How do you feel about 9-eleven?
How do you feel about JSK?
How do you feel waking up every morning looking like a goddamn chipmunk?
Pretty good
What is your problem with
Switch it. Go for your eggs. Get going.
This is nothing.
Light work.
I'm starting for a little bit.
Yeah.
I have one charger for all of my devices. How do I live?
I always I always leave them at work. I leave them at work. Well, yeah, everything is a sea charger
Yeah, that's why they need I always like to spill beer on them or ruin them and
I have an iPhone an older iPhone. So that takes us to
Who killed who killed Jesus by the way a number on that topic who killed Jesus the Romans?
That's that's what I read in the Bible
See him. Yeah, you got sad by a Roman soldier and ribs by a spear
I'm just gonna say
But anyway, I'm not really want to talk about politics religion or sports. People get too defensive. I
Didn't grow up in Saudi Arabia. She did she did grow up in Saudi Arabia. That is very true, but she's not Jewish or Muslim
But she did grow up in Saudi Arabia, that's true. Yeah, that's why it's like she's imported
A lot of people, well, my dad's a little bit arrogant so I mean a little bit of an Egyptian, sorry, I'm thinking something.
If you're worried he's Egyptian so he spoke Arabic.
It's hard to live, it's hard to read because he could speak Arabic.
I want to say hi to your dad the other day when I pulled up and I saw him work outside.
He's not like, he's so dumb.
I don't think you remember him.
He does, he does, and...
Oh
Yo psyche, I'll stop back in a little bit you are
I broke up with you because I thought you were crazy yeah
Likely story I was being like boss
Not like spiteful, but I was just definitely insecure and I was like
Like just like hey, why are you on your phone all the time under a fuck
Like what are you doing bra? I was streaming. I was streaming. No, but then like I was like remember
I think I was mad one day about you and your friendship with Brittany that girl in the oh
Was it at Steve?
Oh, I don't remember at all. I thought you were from your little friend. Oh
No, that was when I was working
Like you were like friends with her like I have I didn't like have a problem with it, but I was like
Skeptical about it, and I don't know why I think ever happened between me and I know like I don't know
I was like insecure at that age, and I was just very much like
but like
I was, you know, granted, I was like, what, 17, 18?
And like, every time anybody brought up Brittany Carmella
and like, I was one of your guy friends or like somebody,
somebody there would be like,
I just want to like, fuck this shit out of here.
I just want to like, excellent.
Yeah, that was a piece of shit when I was younger.
Yeah, but you never said that,
but it was like always somebody like next to you,
like, oh, you're friends with that bitch.
Like, I'm just kind of like.
You know X Y and Z and something like that. I always had a lot more girls as friends
Yeah, right, and you would like laugh. Yeah, I mean like I be being like, you know, it's like 17 or 18
I'm just like yeah
You know what I mean, like it's like everybody like, you know, I mean
When you know, they say that to you
Yeah, because you had the you had the sunflowers on your chest. Yeah, I think I was supposed to be what tattoo I had
I definitely had this one on my ribs. I went to
So much I think I got I think I got this tattoo on my shin when we were dating
OCC and I got five seven cheap and you got me a
Car so cheap. I I never had you. I was I was oh you crashed your car
Where we started dating and then you passed your part of the next day
But like you came and got me before we start it was like when we started seeing each other and
That's why we met yeah, I was going to OCC and I was late for class and like
Me and you start dating and then I just stopped going to this. Yeah, I mean why go to OCC
Yeah
Great
I mean yeah, it was Sandy. Yeah
I
Remember
I crashed I crashed to me. I know I crashed the tibia on and I also crashed the rental and I got the Camaro
But then I didn't I also
Flooded the Camaro flooded during Sandy and then literally I had the rental car remember how to go all the way
It's like my law to go get the rental car
And then and then I they gave me an automatic impala and I totaled that on my way to work
We were like not doing oh, no, dude. We went through like three cards and like a month like
Oh my god, I forget what part did you like a Saturn or something I
Don't ever remember the chief I mean, I don't know if I remember you ever have any car
Do you think we have to work for one?
Oh, yeah, T-bell?
No, probably not.
Oh, that was it.
Bader, LD with my friend.
Justine, I'm not your friend.
All right.
Um, LD, hello, uh,
Oh, what's up, what's up, I just wanted to say, like, uh,
LD, you were just on my panel earlier.
I did, I was on your panel and you, you, you really are.
That was yourself.
But, um, does this lady know that in eight days you're paying five thousand dollars for another lady to come and see you?
she doesn't know that
I got you. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
He was like, do you know that this guy LD is flying out a girl profile number one are gonna repeaters of answering the question
What I think about being a nice boy. Well, you answer the question
What I didn't hear it
Hey dumb it do you know your name is what's your name?
Her name is pretty actually you're not gonna answer the name but also I have a second question ma'am
For you girl, how would you feel you didn't have breakfast this morning?
Hey, what if you if you could have breakfast this morning? I took her out for breakfast the other day
You know we woke up at like two o'clock. How would you feel if you didn't have her answer let her answer
How would you hope you don't have breakfast this morning? I?
Can't hear the first half. He's asking if you how would you feel if you didn't have breakfast this morning?
Yes
I don't know very exactly the same but I didn't unit breakfast this way hungry you fucking retard. Okay. Thank you
I'm done with them
What the fuck you mean to this point?
Yeah, how would you feel if you didn't have breakfast morning?
Howdy, how would you feel?
Fine. I don't make up for it. I don't wake up till like two o'clock in the afternoon anyway, so
It's hard
Get the fuck out of here
Easy work
Go grab a bag of something
Go grab a bag of shit to make it easy
Let us assume you didn't have breakfast this morning
How would you feel?
You dumb fucker
You should have answered the cracker question
I didn't see crackers
You're
Tell me what
Yeah, you know you probably should say hungry if I didn't have breakfast up. I feel hungry. You don't fuck
I gotta give you guys your own arguments against me
I literally have to give you guys even keep up. I gotta give you guys your own arguments
You're too stupid to have it
Yeah, I think ma'am, I think that you're you're a whore. I'm not gonna go ahead and say it. I don't want to be rude
You don't think that you're a dumb ass whore. I think that you smell. I think your hair smells
I think you don't the fucking talking about LD obviously if we are you know
He doesn't know what the fuck you're talking about the fact that he even shows out the proofs all stupid you are
Anything else?
You're too stupid to have a conversation man. Just stop talking. You're stupid to have it.
You chose L.D. dumb dumb.
Your hair is still seeing you chose L.D.
Like clearly I'm not hungry.
Yeah you're retarded ma'am. I'm literally calling you retarded.
I'm not tested but thank you. Do you know what toward it means?
Maybe the helmet on your blush. I'll use short words for you ma'am. I will
And you're just sitting. I use short words not like you're here. You're stinking just like your first time with this
You you know well, ma'am. I can use short words for you ma'am
You know with you because all these hey
Stop go stop. What are you doing attacking the gas stop it go?
Stop it
You can't attack them. No, no, no, I said don't
Divergent instead of Richard I paid to attack them. No
Okay, well, they're saying on it and you have to be nice
Be very rude. I mean I go stop it
Both why that's well really bad. No, you don't
My room
I've been smoking this one and cigarette. So what can I say psyche so like what can I say?
He give her a couple Mac
Fuck you're talking about
If I had a bingo, I would have won. Yeah
You're like, oh
Yeah, I will you call it a retard you don't believe you call it a retard go ahead and call me another retardings
Saxure step. Go ahead. Call me return again. Watch what I have
Go ahead. Call me retard
I just think it's a Larry's that fucking Indian kid came up here to like
I can defend himself sir, is Indian is Indian I can't get your back. Let's run it
Okay, well, you know, I'm not trying to give him plenty fights or anything. I'm just trying to try to have a fuck
Yeah, let's run. I got your back though. Let's run that bitch. No, I'm just chilling. I'm just chilling everybody. Let's just chill
I just want to chill. Come on. They'll be so
Alvin, what's up, Miss Liz?
Because Miss Liz knows that Danielle's going like a little bit. So like what are you doing?
I'm pretty open with a lot of people on here. So can you make it? Would you like to talk? You're not even talking
I haven't like hanging out with you. I'll be be honest with you
Let me talk real quick. Give me like give me like 10 seconds. You've talked a lot of shit and a lot of panels, sir
We're gonna fuck you out a bitch here or not. You've talked. How do you have you not?
You've talked a lot of shit and a lot of panels, sir
of the
you talk about a lot of shit
oh dude you talk about a lot of shit brother
now who?
didn't you do it in like bait
didn't you do it in like betas channel and stuff
like you joined there did you not
did you never join betas channel
no I have joined betas channel
yeah exactly
so big ghost is here now
big ghost is here now what you're gonna do
is you're gonna shut the fuck up
You ain't got talk shit over here. It's like this isn't baby channel. This is big sucks channel and big ghosts is here
It's big brothers here
What do you say goes what do you say goes
Talk a lot of shit
For like what's what kind of big gosses here now? I got like that
Like you say, oh, are you his lover? I'm sex big brother. I got his back. Let's run that bitch
I can show I'm psyched big brother. Let's run it
I've been killing the hunker. Shut up bitch. I'm gonna talk to you. I'm psych's big brother. You're
I'm psych's big brother. You can bring beta. You can bring whoever you want over here. Let's run it. I'm psych's big brother
I'm the big brother
Anybody want to run it?
Are you gonna sit there and shut the fuck up? You caught him retarded. You caught my dude psych all kinds of names
Ain't nobody gonna do it now. Yeah big ghost is over here
I'm the big brother
Ain't nobody gonna say shit about psyche when I'm on here
Well, you know people talk a lot about me, so it's okay
Now big big else is on here now. They ain't gonna talk about now you're
I'm
Scared all the way. My bad. It's like my bad. It's a price. It's a price of fame goes. It's a price of fame, right?
I scared him away. My bad. I'll just be quiet. There's this right there. I think he was on mute.
So how's everyone here?
Okay, no, no, I'm sure not at all just because you ever just ever turn the camera on or you just sit there and bitches with camera
Oh, I have turned it on dumb fuck. What's your argument even if I don't turn on what?
Hey camera
Fucking defeat you. Let's run it. What's your argument? Let's run it
Hey, so I permission or you love your voice. Let's run it
Yeah, I'll turn my camera. I'll destroy you. I'll turn my camera off. I'll fucking destroy you
Why don't you run over to Bayer's channel or something like come back over here, please?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, big cycle's going on. I'm his big brother. I'm his big brother
You didn't have to pick on my little brother. What do you mean here?
No, I didn't get a big dog around here
Yeah
Would you like me to repeat it what you what do you want you don't talk you're not gonna make an argument
You're never gonna beat us. I'm gonna talk to this guy instead of God
No, dude, Gotti is way more interesting Gotti. He's gonna get his ass. Well
Everybody fucking let's run it. Let's run that bitch. I'll get some more money. Let's fuck keep it over for a note
Thank you
For real you're me like everybody
Why don't you join psyches panel talk shit about me go three
You're just mad where I'm from you're here doesn't matter. What's your argument?
You're in me
But if we actually ask around for him I can tell you I ain't gonna tell a bitch like you
Can you sit there and talk shit about other people on different people's hands?
Hey, Saki, don't let them run you like that
Let's run that let's run it
Saki, let's run it
No, no, I love
You heard
I've never said anything before. I'll put you on a shirt homie. You want to run it?
I don't know
You got something be a good boy, aren't you gonna run but you ain't gonna run hey big ghost
That's my name. Check me out and I got
It goes to how old are you any hints?
Not like I could believe them, but
Well, how is your how is your mom?
I'm on my mom is dead
Well, I'm about there too
But that wasn't the question argument, so I'd rather you answer me
Don't ask me no stupid ask question. Don't ask me no stupid question
Ask me my mom
Hey big ghost is here now. You ain't gonna bully psyche anymore big dogs here now bully me
You're not gonna bully me what you're gonna do all of you are gonna shut the fuck up listen
You ain't gonna bully nothing
of the
I know I'm on the
Now would you like to debate ma'am? I love a little piece of you. Actually your boyfriend can keep the piece but I'd love to debate
If you're too fucking stupid to have ma'am, maybe you shouldn't smoke up at all
your
You know when they're like kings are talking to shit, you know when it's
You know, maybe you should like know your place and be quiet
Oh
What do you mean shut the fuck up make your fucking debate what's debate about why should I shut the fuck up go ahead
Man, I guarantee any be a cold day in hell before you ever make me shut up. Go ahead though. Take your chance, man
Open panel go ahead. I
Fuck you
Let's run it
I like how you're voluntarily one of my boyfriend.
I like how cocky you are when you're talking, but when a man talks, when a man talks, you shut up there and you shut the fuck up.
I'm not a keeper.
Okay, let's debate about it. You know what? That's very fair. Let's debate about it.
Your brother
Press underwear. Hmm. My brother psyche. He's gay. It's like he's gay. It's like he's fridious. Look. What do you want to say about him?
What do you want to say about him?
Is that your argument
You ain't gonna fuck with psyche you aren't gonna fuck with psyche you guys know better big ghosts here. Let's run it
So what's your problem psyche go ahead?
You fucking stupid hey dumb dumb you look like a Tarzan
And my girlfriend
Is that your girl is that your boyfriend? Oh, hey, I don't want to miss gender anyone
She's my sponsor
I'm at her and hard as she's drugged out. She's twitching. I don't care. Anybody want to talk shit about psyche cuz now big ghost is here
now we sit up close next to a computer
You know, but yeah, maybe we've actually out in the world
And I'll run it with them
that's what I'm going to say
I don't want to turn your camera on.
Turn your camera on.
She wants to see what you look like.
She's so cute.
Mr. I want nothing to do with her.
What if I just turn my camera off until you turn your camera on?
Sounds good.
Exactly. Let's both run it like that.
What would you like to debate about?
I'm not a bitch like you and I like to keep my camera on.
I'd like to let you know who the fuck I am
You won't he won't you're not a bitch you're not a bitch. Hey listen, sir. You're not a bit star. You just don't know what the fuck you're talking about. I
Know exactly what I'm talking about
Okay, go next one. You ask me if I knew it's Bergman
You know what spur means you read you read your fucking comments. You don't know what that means
Like I said, I don't I never have like this aggressive attitude towards people. It's a lot of these guys in the internet
Oh, I'm sorry. Oh, I wasn't even it wasn't even at you. Oh, it was actually people that treated like you like it
Am I talking to you dumb dumb that's exactly
you fucking retard
you fucking porn star, a fucking whore
I mean I wouldn't be checking this whore then
I am who's keeping score the only person. Yeah, you'd like to make money running your mouth
The only person I know is you're fucking that girl there. She runs her mouth for money here. Yeah, that's not really count
I had to make an account for that, but it was the video of her stuck in my day
Like you have to like go to my day. Just psyche. Can I crush you? They have to be
I'm trying to be easy on the idea, but I actually like to be easy.
Oh, didn't tag someone.
You want it? Let's fucking run it.
All right, this is easy work.
Saki, I'm trying to be easy.
Can you give me the background or like I...
There was like...
Oh, do you want it for real?
it's not me, she wants the camera on, she wants to see what you want
oh, she wants to, let's run up
can I, can I have permission to run it for the female
I like when guys talk to me like this and like to grieve me, so like I'll let them know
yeah, but you do when they like spit on you and slap you and you suck your dick, you fucking whore
yeah
spit it, you're not
You're not a debater. You don't the fuck you're talking about
The fact that you're his girlfriend is fucking weird because you don't even know how to say here and chill and even talk
You're nothing but a whore. You're nothing but a junkie. You don't the fuck you're talking about
If you wanted to date me, I would I would psyche will gladly look we go 1v1 if you want to we even
Or you're gonna sit there and be a girl and shut the fuck up dumb dumb. You don't the fuck you're talking about you're
Maybe you should go somewhere else my hey psyche arrest my piece by the way. Hey, I'll be you fucking bitch
You're the same
Oh fuck it psyche. I'm gonna crash on my dude. It's getting annoying. Yeah, you're the same as you're this no
You're a fucking bitch, too
You know nothing better than you got with a fucking whore that knows nothing. You don't the fuck you're talking about
You're not gonna talk to me like that
not going to talk the psyche like that if you want to let's run it i'll debate anybody let's run it
he left okay well you know anyway like i so it goes he's wait where was he saying that about me
he said something about me sorry i cracked i crashed out sorry i asked him no it's okay
did but did he really say something about me like that he did oh who all do you yeah
Don't know but I know he's part of that. He joined those people. I don't know if he said anything about you know
I did crush. Okay. Oh my god
Yeah, he's right those people because he's like so I mean it's like so funny
It's like when you know somebody like and I defended him to you like over this time like you know, I was like
I don't know. I was like, we don't know what's going on. Okay, everyone is
You brother are you sitting at you on those panels and I agree and I appreciate I appreciate that. Thank you guys
Thank you so much. Yeah
Because uh, did you hear what I said like I have fun doing it?
All right, I have been well play for a little bit of blood. I love to play for a little bit of blood
That's just my game. Let's do it. Let's do it. I didn't mean to run LD off at all or nothing
Yeah, I mean it's like I don't take no shit brother. You gave me permission
How you're being kind of like, you know
play full together, but I guess maybe you take I don't know who to get more seriously or not
But it's you know, I'm sure there's no no bad blood
We're all friends
Let's see
I think we're all friends unless they like go over there
Because you could make the same argument to me like ghosts like you've been over today to channel you have
But what have I done when I've been over there?
I've been here earlier. I'm literally
But when I went over there, I've always debate them
Mm-hmm. You just said oh come on come surprised me, but I say I don't know if she's like mad at me or whatever
I don't I just don't know it's just I don't know. I wouldn't worry about why you work. I wouldn't worry about it
Yeah, I'm okay. I gave me what I said though if anybody wants to come over here and have a little peace a little psyche
I mean, I'm this big brother on his back. Let's fucking run it. Let's debate it. Oh, thank you
They couldn't be really like
Very few people have that body like that back nowadays, but I appreciate those who do so. Thank you very much
You're away betta betta. Yeah
Yeah, so is everybody in in a shadow case or anybody that needs to be okay, so the Tom flash is talking about me, okay?
Let me say now. I mean
We have we know and then Tom flash said he like you know to try to take down my panel and so it's a and then
Yeah, and then um, then it's just like one after one person after the other it's like, um, who else?
Uh, I don't know good times. I don't know. Did you really seem to hate me now? So it is okay. It's okay
Um, let's run it. I got you back brother. Let's run it
Oh, yeah, so canada dry was like talking about me. You're not you're not gonna lose. I guarantee that you're not gonna lose
Thank you
I like I think I like having like having you as an advocate. It's like, uh, oh, yeah
Where you want to go like who's talking shit about you, let's run it. Let's go over there. Well, it is like, you know
I'm not I'm not really like it's okay. I don't I'm not gonna like try to go after people that's I just
I just don't mind my own business. Oh, oh, hold on. You just got five dollars for a super cool psyche emoji. Oh
Okay
I congratulate you, but I don't see your you have a membership. So what are you talking about? Hey, you know, so just
You didn't say you he said he said it was that he said it was LD. Justine. Are you a
Or unless I don't know
I guarantee justine can come up here and debate herself if that's actually her
She's cool, but hey, where you want to go psyche? Let's run that bitch who was talking shit about you
Let's say you know like a lot of people, but I love most of them are even content creators
Let's run it. I'm not mad. I'm not mad at anybody. I don't care
Yeah, the big brothers here big doses here now
Well, I think I appreciate you. Thank you
Oh my gosh, okay, so you really like okay. Thank you. Justine. Yeah. Oh, hey, you're back. I'm sorry Christine. Here you go
I'm so sorry. Hi Christine cool. You can't just you know. Oh, I know her you kicked her out
You didn't hi that's Christine not justine
Christine this is Christine Chris
Christine's awesome goes to be be nice. Oh Christine
You know site that you're probably the last channel and only channel that he is welcome that
Good
It was very fucking rude by the way, are you talking about me?
I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I'm just telling him. I
There is not a single panel. You're not gonna run it with us. Are you? I'm not running you because you're a fucking idiot
You all you don't even know how to have a conversation. Let's run it. Let's run it. You're a fucking idiot
You take everybody off of panels
That is all you ever do. I have psyches back and I'm done
Are you?
Go ahead good and explain how do you have his back?
I'm here fighting his battles
Some immature
Unable to see one having his back
Thank you
I run for the fight. Have I not been saying psyche? Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's join
Brothers and I have his back
Yeah, it's touching as it is goes. Yeah, I can defend myself and it's like, you know
But I got your back brother
Yeah, and I appreciate you feeling that yeah, I'm sorry shares back the fuck up thing now you have your own back
Then you can talk shit about me
I'm saying I'm saying thank you
I said I really appreciate that sentiment and it's like even though I could buy my own battles
I just appreciate you look it up for me like that. It's like not a lot
Try your own battles, but wouldn't it feel good to have somebody in your corner, dude?
We haven't had it for years and years
And now you've got a big brother here. Don't you not had anybody in this corner for years. What the fuck do you been?
But you're not you might have been here, but you're not battle with them like I am
Well, Christine has been there since you see the you know what I've had to
But I'm here battling with him, but you are being
How are you thinking people are out there you're paranoid
People are not out there to get
Where would you do where do you think you would even what's your problem with me? What why you have a problem with me?
You know when you start calling people whores and women
Like you she wasn't a horse you might have been a whore I'm here to have psychies back
Do you realize that you yeah, we don't know who cares you chase who cares
LD is also one of his supporters
No, I I haven't seen any money. I've been here as long as LD
So how supporting is he? I
Mean
Not everybody has money
like he knows this. Yeah. It's
like it's like there's a lot of
ways to support the show. I'm
happy just even people be nice
supports the show. Okay. Yeah.
Even even people have gone after
you. Watch your argument. Okay.
LDS. That's fine. That's fine.
It's night tonight and I guarantee
he'll be back in 30 minutes. He'll
be back. Why are you tripping?
What's your argument?
I don't have to
We'll be back. Everything is not an argument
Not every one of you make an argument and don't fuck. Why are you making an argument won't be calling it?
Go shit, it's okay. Please don't call Christine names, please
Respect respect the panelist. That's one of the rules. Okay, that's right
Yeah, I'll be respectful
Thanks. Thank you. We can talk to each other. They're not way here. They're enough
Hey, but I didn't make a care. What's your point though?
I
Want to see the tarot card I made today like I'm here
This might fit the third one here to make a ghost tarot card. Yes
I will wait. I did my third one. I've made so there's see kind of
It's like a beta card in that you can't see that we see
There's Muhammad and you know what Christine? I will apologize to all of these that make you feel better
I'm talking to go to the site, not you.
Anybody that wants to beta anybody that wants and justine's not and justine won't come up here because of you
I'm his big brother. I don't give a fuck shit about
I win
You ain't nobody
I can I can I'll I can I'll debate you and I can help you send him
Sometimes it does come down to that
To a fist fight but if if you had a fist fight I'd rather have Mike Tyson in my corner correct and I might Tyson then
I got his back. Okay. So, you know, if I step down it would be you and him
Okay. Yeah, we have a good fucking time. Yeah, okay. Good. I'm glad you'll have a good time because
Only channel you get to go to anymore nobody wants you on your on their panels because you chase everybody else away
What don't you understand about that? Well, if they fuck with psyche, I do tend to chase them away if they fuck with psyche
Yeah, it's not a bad thing. LD and his female friend were not fucking with psych
And you wouldn't shut up. Would you would you like me to apologize to LD and his female friend?
Would that make it better?
No, what makes it better is that you don't start to fit with people
No fucking I got psyches back fuck that they start shit with him fuck it. Let's run. They didn't start shit with psyche
LD comes up here at night and has
Conversations with people his bitch, but did she well that was rude. Did she run her mouth?
No, no, she wasn't really saying anything, but you know what? But then somebody did say
You know what? I will I will I will apologize. What's that foreign? I'll apologize
Nobody fears
You don't care them. Why are you still written your mouth about it? I apologize
What's your problem
You want a debate, and I know you do I any way site
Yeah, I had that well yeah, I had to
Apologize what else you I roll over and saw you here
I'm up for a minute. Appreciate what the fuck you're talking about man
You stupid to have the conversation. Hey, Christine's awesome. Um, she doesn't know how to talk any other way, psych. We've all gotten used to it. Oh, man, would you like?
That's why nobody wants him on the channel. I'm glad you're here. Nobody wants me. Oh, that's fair. Oh, that's hurtful.
The truth hurts sometimes, doesn't it?
Love. I always win.
Nobody cares if you win. You know that, right?
But I didn't have psychies back tonight, and I want to smoke
What's it like you need his back about what's it's like?
Well, listen to them when he's asked me a question you've got to have
Yeah, you gotta listen when I'm talking bait on all them. We're talking shit about him
No, they weren't and I yes, like yeah, let's go back over there. Let's warm it
Doesn't need you and he and he is welcome. It beat us at any time. Yeah. Yeah
I went over I went over there and it just seems like my name was being brought up in chat and
Unless you have a good
I know I know, but it's only one or two people and you can't please
You know that I mean out of fifty-six
Words are hateful
I
You said it before it's new. It's a new concept. Yeah, but you're my net layer you talk
Is that what people are mad about is like that I like you know
that's why but I think I think I think they might think that I'm charging people because
I did something try something where I was like I did it well bitch I'll tell them to their face
I don't think they're understand I don't think anybody I mean there's a few of us because we
were here when you first started it yeah I was here too
I don't want you to know why understanding what it is like like earlier when you
So guys I did just put in the channel description. I put the full instructions for
clapping and
And I just don't think people are understanding the sponsorship thing like earlier when when page was up here
It was just you and page and in page like why isn't anybody joining and I think other people thought that they had
Would you like to give $10?
Yeah, I was I tried to try to explain it is the u.s
Up I just put a little pinch on that saying that you know the panel the panel is just for one at a time
He was getting mad
and
I don't think they're understanding what you're doing because you like having the one-on-ones
And that's when you close the panel and then you continue to the one-on-ones until
Somebody wants to sponsor the
My understanding of sponsoring the panel is that you know
Somebody pays the one-to-one. He closed it. Can you go ahead and name one? Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let her talk, please.
Somebody
Somebody somebody pays to sponsor the panel everybody gets to come up whether it's you or Ted
And I just don't think people like earlier
I think they all felt they had to pay to come up at the same time
So nobody paid. Name one person, well I'm going to infer here, I'm going to go handle this, but it's like you let me handle this.
Name one person that paid to come up tonight.
Page.
Name one person.
page
You guys are trying to bully sucky, but now I got his back. Fuck all that
Maybe some misunderstanding
Because I'm not going to have this misinformation. Do you feel?
Christina's really
This is okay. It goes this is my panel. You're sponsored the panel and like you can I want you to like
Respect this respect the rules of the panel. I help enforce them for me not like you know go after people's not supposed to be like
Shit, what are up here? Let us let me at least debate her
Who do you want to be one there's nobody there's nobody there's oh Chris is right here
I don't want to talk to you then why did you join?
Because I wanted to talk to psych. It's his channel. No, no fuck that. You ain't gonna bully psych anymore. It goes
She's not bullying me. He's not bullying me. Okay. She's not at all Christina's like my she's like really she's a sweetheart
She's always always have my back. She's really she's really really good friends. Please. Please don't be mean all right
Let's run the bill. Let's forget her. Let's run the panel. He's never he's never ever ever done anything
Let's forget her
I gave
I even offered to pay but she don't want to see Christine that's Christine's a true a true friend
She is I consider Christine a true friend. Well, I was just like beta was your friend
You fucking made the argument against me. Look what happened. It is
I'm your true friend. I'm your true brother. I'll have your back. No matter what
I want to have friends. I want to have the truth. I really want to have your two puns like a lot like
Back no matter what
I love the debate. I'll debate any of them. They're fucking without her. Let's have a good time with you. You feeling good?
Yeah, but it's like I think like there's like there's a there's a homophobic in the community
I think
About it, man. I'm not I'm not
You know, I think I'm doing okay. I'm doing okay. Let's have a good wrestler at night, man. At least another hour, right?
Yeah
I'm going to drop down. But like I said, thank you for seeing us. Bye bye. Bye bye, Christine.
I'm going to shout out to your dog. And it's a new concept. That's all I think it is. Thank you, Christine.
You were just over there talking about it. Were you on the channel? You were just Christine. Were you not just talking about my boy?
Was I Jen yeah, I did you were I know you were she was
Not she was not she would not do you were over there even if you didn't join the fucking panel you were in the comments
Yeah
No, I don't know what you look like. Yeah, you were that was yeah, you know, I was not
Everybody trying to beat up on psyche. What's the what's your problem? It's like
Go ahead join. What's your problem? Okay? It's okay. It's okay. I don't have a problem. I don't need to be I'm sure I'll talk to you later, psyche
We're almost there because you're about our dish or strike my man's
Ain't nobody likes psyche unless you want to I like I like how you're like about it. I'll fuck and run it
Yeah, but nobody's going to vote debate because it's like people that don't have a really good thing
really good. It's like, yeah, if I wasn't here, they would be doing it. They would be doing it.
Yeah, they would be. Like, they did it today with Paige. But I got you back, brother.
Are we not brothers? I mean, Paige is, Paige is, Paige is, you know, cool. And then, uh,
that there's some people. I would love to hear from Paige. As long as she don't pull far. But I
love to hear from Paige. I think, I think she's doing a show right now. I think she's, she's running
Um, yeah, for you wins the P. You know, I'll back her. Hey, so I hear on your own. I'll back up brother. My bad
I just I know you're you know, you're you know, you're you know, you know
Can I ask you one question? Yeah, did anybody fuck with you tonight? Did I not have your back?
Yes, you did nobody did nobody gonna debate that shit. Yeah, nobody said nobody said very much
But hey psyche, you know, I feel about that fucking like you know, I feel about that like Tarot shit
We don't agree with it. I got your back then ain't nobody gonna fuck with psyche number on here
Yeah, and I know you yeah, and I appreciate that it makes me feel good that you you care and I appreciate you
Okay, baby. Oh, you always you've always let me join you boys have my back. We might have had some disagreements
But yeah, I'm gonna have you back. Let's run it. I want some of data now at this point
I feel like you want you don't do it tonight
Did you do what what do you want to do?
Well, I want some of data
You had to bait a little bait. Oh, be you want to go to beat me. I want some of her
Well, she was she was in the cat earlier and she was like, oh come she's a come come surprise me at my piano
Now what she did was she talked shit to you but I'm here now better talk shit to you now
Well, I don't know you want to join a joke. I think she may have making a joke like that you would
I don't fuck it. Let's run it. She ain't gonna talk. She ain't gonna make a joint joint joke now. Let's run it
Well, I
People I know I'm used to you know, not everyone be everyone's cup of tea, you know
It's like I am I can't I'm just saying if you want to run it. I got your back, bro
Thank you. Appreciate that
Yeah, I mean, I'd say and I I'd use like say that I do stand up for myself
But it's like I'm really like, you know, sometimes I get annoyed big ghost is here now. I got your back. Let's run it
No, let's run it. I guarantee you. We'll fucking win. I
Guarantee you win. I'm a big ghostie. Let's run it
Let's do it. No, I don't know what does that mean though? I don't know what is a run it's what does that mean?
Let's join beta's conversation. Let's join her live. I guarantee you will fucking win
I mean, it's like, I don't know if she wants us to like come in there and start like, you know, arguing
and stuff like that, I don't want to...
Fuck it, let's just run it, hey fuck it, let's just run it.
Oh, you're crazy, you're so funny, come on, go, it's okay, you know, go to your own...
Come on, come on, Si.
I want her. You don't want to do it. You don't want to do it.
You can go. I'll go. I'll go. I'll go have a look. I'll go watch it.
You know, I, I don't want to bother her. Like, you know,
You don't want me to join by myself? Remember when Emma, like I,
like, sent people to Emma's and then all of a sudden, like,
You don't want me to join. Like, hey, listen, I'll do it right now.
I'll fucking run it. I want you to come with me.
Okay. I mean, I always go watch. I'll talk shit about you.
Okay, well, I think I don't really want to say
I can just see this kind of exploding where she's like what the fuck you said you go is we can't talk to me
I'm gonna so I think I'm not gonna I'll fight. Oh, you know, I think it's okay. I don't want to cause an argument about me
I'm already gonna see my kick me brother. Oh
Well, I hope not, you know, it's like, you know, if you yell it that they will you know, so we want to
These are these are inside places
Well, you join and then when you get kicked I got you back. I'll come right up. Thank you
Thank you
Okay, well at two o'clock, let's do it. I don't know if she'll still be on it too, but
Yeah, that'd be fine
Um, we can just go over that but I do I do want to make it a friendly thing and not like where he's like
You know debated her unless it's like, you know, you know, it's friendly debate. I don't want I don't want you like accusing
Yeah, you want me to run? Hey, it's like you're on your own data channel right now. I'll do it right now
Well, I see the thing I don't want to invade I just
Go ahead
I just let you do your thing. Oh my gosh, but yeah, I don't, I don't, I encourage it, but...
Wow, so yeah, I uh...
I'm having an interesting time though.
I hope everyone's doing okay in the chat.
Let me see.
At two o'clock, the panel is,
you know, it says on the scroll,
it says how long it will last until 2 a.m. EST.
It's 310.
Yeah, but it has to be 2 a.m. here.
It's only 111 here.
Hey, are you drunk, ghosts?
Oh, yeah, it wasn't good. He's okay. He's left forbidden. Okay. Well, you know, it is it's just like I'm I'm just gonna play
I'm gonna play my video again here in the case in the case and nobody's seen it
Here's my new video the new introduction to the show you watch this real quick
Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up the scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Scythe twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boo splashing on cam chat losing their minds Michael
getting gong Alex taking flight it's wild it's wrong and we do it every night
Paige got him simping hearts in the chat but she ain't got time for a dude like
that diamond flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show party no
filter all facts yo
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex tried a joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes
Slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow no rules just rolls
We pretend to play one hand on the mute of the letting it spray
wrong word and we're trending in the press welcome to the madness buckle up tight
boobies flashing on cam chat losing their minds michael getting gong to alex taking flight
it's wild it's wrong and we do it every night page got him simping hearts in the chat but she
ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard like the girls react it's a freak show party
Lights out, one more round, beat is on the line, yelling at a ghost from a bottle of wine, we laugh, we cry, we crash, rewind, same time next week, you know the vibe.
Thank you. I'm glad you liked it. Thank you so much. I'm a loser at the loser. Thank you so much
I was pretty fucking. I think it was pretty cool
Oh, oh my gosh
Fucking ghost
Oh my gosh ghost
You're supposed to approach very very sweet and kind and not
I hope he didn't say my name. That was hilarious
You like the second one?
Oh, the other one I did, or the second, which one?
I also did one for a shorter one.
I know it's not funny, but usually yelling so loud here,
I'll show you this other one here.
From the shadows of the sub conscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls. This is psyche awakens
crowd
Yo, welcome to the madness buckle in tight tarot on deck third eye in flight truce get told he goes unfold
We start a soul with a tea surf cold panels be popping trolls be dropping
Spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
Slighty Awake can step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's soul-deep play
Now grab your teeth and slay the dead
Slighty Awake can stomp, look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Hi, I apologize. I apologize actually for a ghost. I'm sorry. I apologize. That wasn't very nice with him
He's kind of he's like that. This is personality. I'm sorry
It's the guy that gave you the terror
Yeah, well, I was talking about the guy that was talking
Yeah, he left he left he went over to beat his chat
I apologize. I'm sorry. That was not very nice. That's not audio. You don't need to apologize
I'm sorry. I like I'm sure I pushed him because I was like, I love you so much. So like, you know, I think you got him
You started kind of triggered. Yeah, I'm sorry
It's clear
You're Alex here. Hey, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, Alvin and company? Oh
Hmm
You know what I've been waiting to say to LD for like a month every time he cams up if you put the green hat with the L
That's Luigi
That's Luigi and Mario
Yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely with the mustache
When you take the glasses off I in the hat on the hell. I'm like, yo, that's Luigi
I'm just talking with you, but that's fine. I don't like the Celtic
One day he just had come out on an angle
He was like turned to the left of something he had he didn't have the glasses on he was smoking a cigarette the mustache
I can't grow out of my hair is my hair is like too thin to grow a fucking mullet
I don't think I could do it
I used to have long hair until the motorcycle accident
They had to they had to cut off my hair when they drilled it to my head
I'd be able to shave like certain parts, so like at that point I just basically cut my
whole head off. There's certain parts of my hair, like my scalp that does grow there.
When I get my fade, you can see the fucking holes in the back, like in the front, you know?
I mean, like it looks like my hair is thinning, it's just like...
you know I try to your hair is fine don't worry no but like if I don't have like my bangs like I
you can see that my hair looks thin it almost looks like you can see through it but that's
because I have a bunch of scars that I can't grow hair from. As you grow older the hair starts
I've got really good genes.
You can take me to page shopping.
We go to page shopping.
And like, I will probably always have this long hair.
But it means everything.
Good genes means everything.
I've never done that before.
Grandfather and all my grandfathers had hair.
Because they were like 99.
So I think I'm good.
You both look very on the outside.
I usually shave.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I shave.
I usually shave.
You both look very young.
I know you're older than little.
Little baby.
like my dad's was like he's Italian mixed with like Egyptian so like we've got like really really
thick I've got like mixed hair my brother's how I was gonna ask you about that I see some girls
with that hair it looks like natural on top and then it gets like kind of like rastafarian looking
well yeah that's like the same hair with like extensions
Some of it is old extensions and some of it is my hair
But my hair is in dreadlocks like this. I'll show you where my real hair is not like
So it's a style. It's a thing like I never knew about it. It's my hair. I like I like the glow-in-the-dark ones
But it's basically like what it what dreadlocks are is just like a million dots like put into one like per section
Right, but it doesn't match like the top of your hair like your top hair is like
I haven't dyed it and I haven't like ripped it. I haven't done the deadlocks yet
I haven't like knotted it to each other to form them yet. So like I do that
I'm supposed to keep up with it. I don't come lately. So I look like
You know, I end up with these roots that I would just find it cool like two cultures mixed in one head
Like that, you know, it's definitely what's up, Jamie?
Because it's it's waving and it's very like, uh, it's like trying to
I don't want to try to be white, but it's definitely, it's very nappy, it gets matted so easily, so it will pop up with its own hair.
It's your hair.
Yeah, yeah, it's very like it's like pinky wavy curls. That's a very strange thing. Yeah, but they're very thin for dreadlocks like
Yeah, well like you can there's different ways to form dreadlocks, but new
Traditional like it was like I mean I don't know how you form them, but I additional dreadlocks
Yeah, everybody has different ways of doing their dreadlocks
There's so many different ways you could do dreadlocks, but like if you free form dreadlocks
They're gonna where like you let them was not up on them
by themselves and kind of do their own things. They always end up thicker. Whereas too, it's
like you crochet them with a needle and you were to form them like, you know, started
with a crochet needle, you can control more of like, how thick your threads are.
Are you Jamaican though? Or is it just a thing?
Yeah, like...
Do you a lot usually go with the Rastafari and Jamaican culture?
Um...
Or is it just a thing?
I've never actually done a lot of Rastafari and Jamaican culture, but it's also called
a protective hairstyle usually for black people, and it's not really good for like, you know,
They said that they said that about braiding hair. They said braiding hair with specifically
African and they were like no it's actually the French braid which came from like the Vikings
like they would braid their hair like that's lost like braiding braiding braiding braiding I love
that braiding kid when you go on vacation and like you're making ladies on the beach and they
They call it the French braid.
But you have black, unless I'm just assuming.
How I learned how to do dreadlocks was I used to braid my own hair with, like, cornrows
and stuff like that, and I used to braid my hair in with different hairstyles and that,
with the long extensions like
But people do and I look really white, but I have this like course, you know, like make hair
So it's yeah, like a little bit darker than you. Yeah
Green was moving the door. Go was fucking I'll be just fucking kidding
Oh, these are UV so like the green on the dark. Yeah, the yellow glow in the dark
My hair was this color like all one color before and all this one color before but like I've kind of changed it
Oh, it's nice that you keep some of that. Yeah, I have to because like while working in a club is one thing with UV lights
But like I can't not
Yeah, you know
So I always have to know something
So you just look even hotter in a club old dark and your hair glowing in the dark. It's like a thing
I work in a club and I like to stand out and like not a lot of people have like the bright movie hair
But like I you know, I know how to do hair and I like to like stand out
So like, you know, I always like having to be here and I always have to be like to my room because I'm
Kind of like kids would like I've got the red light
It's just a bright red light.
Is it red? It's not UV, right?
No, it's just red.
Yeah, it's just a red light.
It's like the same, yeah.
It's just red.
It's not even a dark light. It's not even like a red. It's not a little low. It's just I think the glass
Yeah, right. It's not like a photo shop. It's not like a photo room
Yeah, it's not like that like a dark. Yeah, you know, I know it's just like the class of red is up in Korea
Whatever it is. Yeah
I think I'm getting too fucked up. I see Luigi and Princess Peach
No, she's in the next castle. She's in the next castle. I like to think
Oh, you're Zelda
It's a me
Legend of Zelda. That's right on Nintendo. I definitely don't look like fucking goddamn blink
Yeah, I look more likely to be here. You look more likely
I
Look like the NPC you would buy bombs off of
You can be a movie star, like he can be an actor.
If he shaves, he's a completely different human.
He can be Luigi, he can be a mobster.
He could be, you know, this guy had to have a movie star.
I think I'm trying to rock the muscle.
I'm going to start curling it, honestly, in like a week.
Like, it's almost long enough for me to start curling it.
why
You know who he is, I'll show you a picture, but there is only scene to draw it.
Now I like totally want to see a picture of a beautiful couple man
You can be Luigi, yeah, but I got to be in like Zelda I can't be anybody
I'm the NPC I'm the NPC that sells bombs
I'm a they them that's like wings
So like it works. I don't know what you would see in the like that
i don't know i i think that includes elda the same game besides if we're gonna go to the final
fantasy i guess we'll like go find no treasurer in that game no i don't play too good you would be
cypher you would be like i want to be cypher oh we have to write all that i'm sorry but if we're
doing a cosplay like tag team like is it the case that's it was that one no of course but it's cypher
Oh, no, Cypher doesn't. I think it's Zell.
Did you look better?
Yeah, I already knew it was Zell. That's even worse.
Oh, that was close.
Cypher is way cooler than fucking Zell.
No, because Cypher thought it was like huge chicken
and he sounds dumb.
Sounds like I've got fucking hands on chicken.
Yeah, like I think I don't.
Yeah, but Zell's like, they make Zell like mad cheesy.
Like, they like, you know.
Yeah, you could really boost him and she's right about it.
Because character like mad cheesy.
Like, hey, you guys, what's up?
Hell yeah.
Like, you're very, very good.
Cypher's a cool character.
All right, he's a sore loser.
I'd rather I think I'd rather be the elements. I hate it. I can't why does everyone keep on her summer? I see one tattoo
From head to toe and tattoos
Now she's done
I like saying that I'm looking people in the eyes and they're like, oh, yeah, like if they don't know I have tattoos
But like I don't look tattooed me in the eyes. It's like my face tattoo isn't covered up
I don't look like I'm tattooed. I don't either like at all my legs
Like I said people look me straight in the eyes and I'm like, I don't like tattoos. It's like not a good look for me
And I agree. Oh, yeah, like I was only restraining the eyes. Oh, yeah, you're like tattoos. I'm like, oh my god, it's like
No, I have no problem with my legs.
See, what do you got? Feathers? Dights?
I see dice going.
I got, I got full, almost like full legs.
So, it's like...
No.
That's good.
You can cover up with pants.
An eagle. An eagle.
Nice.
An eagle. A dog.
wait that's your dog i remember that european ones that's your dog
he's from new york yeah
he's a real dog he says it's so yeah it's a thick new york accent he's nypd
it's not a vehicle he's a he's sergeant detective
sergeant detective yeah sergeant detective alexander mcqueen
I'm dead serious like
That's number that's number six nine six nine
No, it's actually six eight and you owe me one
Sad that
Forty-third percent and the 48
Sergeant detective police officers Alexander McQueen. He doesn't sound he doesn't sound very Irish to me
I'm not I
You don't sound black either. I'm not black
Yeah
My body
Make something I'm like, yeah
Man, yeah, I like fool I fool the masses. They think I'm like
I was born in Colombia
South America. I came in one of those five years old is my life
So McQueen McQueen is what nationality?
McQueen McQueen is fucking up a designer. That's not my real name
It's not
Yeah, let's end McQueen was a high-end design. He's dead
Honestly, I didn't know that but they were like, yeah, it was into crazy shit, but whatever
Did you ever see Alexander McQueen? Well, one of his ready houses like that. I believe I
Love his sneakers and his jeans man. There are a thousand dollars each but my Jordan's kind of guy
Alex is my middle name. So that's why I use my middle name. I was gifted Puma. I keep it gifted. I have this curse. They're not
Every single month of my life. I don't like that. I that's the thing that I hate Puma because they're from a Nazi company
But I do love their shoes like they make like those the crazy issues I own like I would love for them
And by sneakers
You break your ankle like you prove what you get you you buy Alexander McQueen shoes
You're gonna be in heaven your little toes are gonna be in heaven
Yeah, it's like you know second little heaven pillows for your toes
You think Jeffrey Epstein went to calls Jeffrey Epstein was fucking probably McQueen's best friend
You know how they endorse like Derek Jeter Nike Epstein probably had a closet just for the McQueen gear
Nice and comfy
You know when you buy cheap shit the dye of the clothes kills you
So if you go to a cheap clothing store that buys gear from China
And you put it on and you sweat the dye will steep into your pores
And start giving you cancer
That's why you rich
So like if I want to leave down on the videos that are on my own you said you could but I would have to pay for them and I
You guys are a really cute couple. This is the first day you met
Now I've known her for like 15 years we used to date
Yeah
Yeah, the other day when we went into a store some guy was like, I like your hair and then to hit when he came in next
Oh, yeah
He was like, I like your shoes to hit the same guys. I like your shoes to him
And then they're like he was like you guys must be a couple and like I didn't hear this at the time
But I later found out that he goes. Yeah, no, it's she's my sister
Just and I don't know like
She's not my sister, but some guy was just yeah
And he was like, oh, I like, I saw you was talking to her.
He was like, oh, I like your tattoos.
I like your whatever.
And he saw me with my tattoos and the shoes.
He's like, oh, I like your shoes.
And I'm just like, that's a weird thing to say
to another man, you know?
What kind of man, when another man goes,
I like your shoes.
That usually means you want to fuck.
I told you that.
I told you.
And that's how I see it.
I wasn't trying to be friendly with this guy.
And he's like, oh, you guys look like you're dating
or something.
And I was like, nah, it's my sister.
Compliment
That's why I said that because I was like then he's not gonna say anything to her
He's not gonna fucking disrespect her in front of me, you know right online day. Boom, you know, don't fuck around like you're already telling
No, it's like I want to talk to you in public like I'm here to buy a cigarette and you're just some fucking
NPC along the way never will be what is that?
I don't know the acronym that's got to teach me what that was mpc
Non-playable character like non-playable car
Generated character
Meaning you like you don't mean anything, right? Like I'm going there like the shopkeeper for a fucking blunts and vapes or whatever the fuck
I'm there for and this guy saying something with me along the way, and I'm like, I don't want to talk to you
Like we're doing shit. Yeah, I'm not I'm not a social per I mean, I'm a social person
That's the funny thing I've heard in my life, bro. So everyone around me. It's an MPC
I walk around with that shit like not playable to get away from me not playable character
I just never heard it put in that way
Yo, that's amazing. I
Walk in every store and someone talks to me. I'm like MPC
MPC, but thank you for that. I
Haven't laughed this hard in a while
Woo, Christine get your stupid ass up here. That's not Christine
That's just look at you guys look like brother and sister
Yes, like a couple and that's the best relationship you can ever have
I just said that to throw him off guard and I'm like well
I know he's not gonna say anything disrespectful in front of me and like towards her knowing that let's to be honest
I'm so glad you're on board
So awesome. Oh
He's alive Pat came
Yo rewind that and see how Pat just rolls from the day
Did you he just like?
Yeah
You would have some good apps
Yeah, I can't deal with this big baby and J1. I can't deal with this. Yo
Yo
What's going on? Yo, are you an MPC? Yes, oh, yo, I had to come up. I just heard you
I just pulled up like Timon niggas talking about some MPC. Just found out some MPC shit. Yo, you're crazy, bro
That's the point of your shit
Yo
Yo, I'll be you frozen yo, Jay you there
That's Louie
Someone was giving me a call someone was giving me a call and I had to answer it
So like I was just about to say I'm so glad you're on the same like you're on the same level as me where it comes
To like being in public and it's like don't talk to me
Don't do x-y and z and like it's not that like I'm not a social person
I got shit to do
You know
I'm not like an anti-social person or not friendly, but between my job and then the amount of people that come up to me just because like in New Jersey I'm different looking, the amount of like, times of day, it's like, attention.
Yeah, and like, I know I do, so like, I'm ready for it, I'm not complaining about it, because like, I'm aware of the way I look myself look, thus, you know, I know I'm going to get the attention, not going to be like, why is everybody going to be attention, I have no idea, like, I know I make myself stand out, but.
It just gets so I'm not trying to be rude, but it just gets so tiring doing the same thing over and over again
And it's just like I don't want to be rude and be like take another lap
But I also if I stopped to say like paragraphs to everybody that had something to say to me
I would just like have nothing left. That's what I'm saying
They're they're like, oh did you just find her on the side of the road and bring her home?
And I'm like, no, I've known her for like 15 years like
But like also like it wasn't like a lot of people like when they first meet you they're like oh you're so rude or like you're so
Intimidated you're so
Don't talk to me. Don't talk to me. I'm like I'm not rude or mean to other people like I don't I don't roll my eyes
I'm not very social because it's just like draining like it's like you know
Like you know the amount of attention it does get and then the amount of attention me and you both get in public is just like
even more
Off the wall so like I'm so glad that you see that you're not like oh you're a bitch
You know what I mean, and you're just like we're or you're anti-social. I don't know time to stop and talk to this guy for 20 minutes
I'm not trying to get his number like
I could only come up with I'm sure he'll be talk to me because he was trying to talk to you and then he was like
Oh, this guy walking out
I don't know. He was giving everybody
I'll be I'm gonna keep it above. Yo, how close was he to you guys?
Like what's the
Today, I mean we know no no no no the guy the guy at the gas station. I'm saying now we just fucking
That's what I'm saying like what's the distance like was he four feet away from you two feet away from oh
No, he was in fighting distance. It wasn't gun distance. Oh, yeah, yo, you should have
He was like holding the door open like we were walking it
because I guess that's a weird thing to say to another man is I like your shoes
There are really great shoes. I don't think I don't feel I've walked out right my shoes are
Shoes with that guy's style. So like I kind of like halfway. I'm just like I feel like he just like inserted
You know what I mean seeing that you like cringy shoes because you walked in after me
I don't think he saw you until later. That's when he decided to add in nice things after you walked in
He was like, oh, I like oh, oh
Yeah, so like I had no idea you said the
Sister like I just you didn't know I heard I thought you said like my sister got them for me
I heard the word sister and you know I heard that's my sister when he was like are you guys a couple you heard
Yeah, no, I didn't hear that my sister
I thought when he said something about your truth to you
I thought he said like my sister got them for me or something something my sister because I can't hear very well
And I usually read lips that I didn't turn around to see or hear exactly what you said all I heard was sister
So I assume
I was just like he's not gonna
When you said I thought you said something about like your sister picking out your shoes for yours or thank my sister
So I just said they're like
Uh-huh having no idea what you said a little later on when you told me we got out of the gas station
Really what you said to that guy and I was like, oh, I'm your sister now
Like I I just stood there like bobbing my head like, uh-huh. Yes, sir
It was just weird this fucking rando is like are you guys a couple and I'm like what the fuck is that you're your business?
Like what so so what you think you just Mac on her in front of me like
No, I'm not saying that like
like there's some guys that like straight up like you should see some guys like what they say to me like
flat out like some guys say just crazy shit like this one guy i was literally okay
Disregard, but I was dumpster diving right like we all do that. Yeah, but like in New Jersey
It's like weird and you are the LD LD next time bro. Just punch the niggas
I've done that before I've done that before in Vegas. I'm dead
Actually with that Mill Hill it was at Mill Hill in front
Some guy was talking to my girl, bro, and she had a she was ordering us all drinks we sent her to the bar to go
Go get us drinks. It was Sam this girl Sam Sholo
How old were you? How old were you?
So you died no before I moved to Vegas like 22 23. Yeah, and we were at a
And some guy was some guy was talking to her and he had his lips pierced like both sides like snake bites
So I walk up next to my like tap them on the shoulder. I'm like, you know, and he turned around
I'm like does that does that hurt and I point to his lips. He's like not really
I'm like not you the guy who's dick you're sucking and I just started punched him in the fucking face as fast
As hard as I could
and she came up to me not not her this is another girl but at mill hill and she was like
fucking why'd you start hitting them i'm like i i saw you talking to him and i didn't like it like
she's like oh well you know we were just talking about the yankees or whatever when the devil takes over
us right i was like i did yeah but like i did we come out of our face again i never saw that
We have lost the devil
Now I'm gonna shoot everybody gotta control that monster man. That's my shit
You guys are muted, there you go.
Yeah.
All right, now we're unmuted.